<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>暖暖写作空间-Writing on 心暖</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C%E7%A9%BA%E9%97%B4-writing/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 暖暖写作空间-Writing on 心暖</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>zh-cn</language>
        <copyright>心暖</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 06:27:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E5%86%99%E4%BD%9C%E7%A9%BA%E9%97%B4-writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>G9 Writing Assignment: Eleven</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/g9-writing-assignment-eleven/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 06:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/g9-writing-assignment-eleven/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sandra Cignero&amp;rsquo;s short story &amp;ldquo;Eleven&amp;rdquo; uses uses characterization to illustrate an adolescent&amp;rsquo;s struggle to shape their identity to conform with social expectations. The author uses the speech of Rachel and Mrs. Price to demonstrate that society does not want for one to mature, however, it simply forces arbitrary expectations onto one. When Mrs. Price notices that Rachel has pushed the red sweater onto the very tip of the table, she exclaims, &amp;ldquo;You put that sweater on right now and no more nonsense.&amp;rdquo; In an attempt at rebellion against the teacher, she said, &amp;ldquo;But it&amp;rsquo;s not -&amp;rdquo; However, she was interrupted by a harsh &amp;ldquo;Now!&amp;rdquo; from Mrs. Price. The fact that Mrs. Price uses the word &amp;ldquo;nonsense&amp;rdquo; to describe Rachel&amp;rsquo;s refusal to touch the sweater, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not hers, shows that her teacher is not willing to listen to Rachel&amp;rsquo;s childish explanation. In this scenario, Mrs. Price does not show understanding to Rachel&amp;rsquo;s situation, which is indicated in the story by her refusal to listen to Rachel&amp;rsquo;s explanation. Mrs. Price imposes the expectation on Rachel that she should stop fussing around and simply &amp;ldquo;put that sweater on.&amp;rdquo; The author uses the word &amp;ldquo;but&amp;rdquo; coming from Rachel to signify her attempts to correct the misunderstanding. But, the teacher&amp;rsquo;s complete ignorance, exemplified by her refusal to allow Rachel to complete her sentence, indicates that she simply wants Rachel to conform to her expectations. The lack of communication between the two shows how the social expectations involuntarily imposed on Rachel does not wait for her maturation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>John Locke Essay Competition 2023</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/john-locke-essay-competition-2023/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 06:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/john-locke-essay-competition-2023/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Awarded a High Distinction in the Junior category of the John Locke Institute&amp;rsquo;s 2023 Global Essay Competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-something-important-about-which-nearly-everybody-is-wrong&#34;&gt;What is something important, about which nearly everybody is wrong?
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humans have a deeply rooted fear of the unknown and a desire for security amidst uncertainty. STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics) disciplines, as a field of study and specialization, seem to provide some control over life&amp;rsquo;s unpredictability, and are thus highly valued in contemporary society. At the same time, the humanities, which call us to lean into the inherent uncertainty of life, are often diminished in value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The underlying attitude that explains people’s overvaluation of STEM and that has led nearly everybody to choose a STEM subject as a college major is wrong. This attitude is important to correct, for its unquestioned adoption indicates that society is not seeing technology as a mere tool, but, instead, is unwittingly using it to further dehumanize and instrumentalize us. In this essay, I will explain the origins of this attitude and make the case that it ought to be course corrected with the deliberate study of humanities, so as to steer the future of STEM in an ethical direction. Firstly, I will provide an overview of the historical trends underlying the choice of pursuing a STEM major and government initiatives to push citizens to study STEM. Secondly, I will explain how the decline of interest in the humanities is caused by an overestimation of  the power of STEM. Thirdly, I will argue that our overvaluation of technology has allowed it to instrumentalize and dehumanize us. Finally, I will explain why, in the face of technological instrumentalization, the study of humanities is essential to guide STEM in a morally correct direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-decline-of-the-humanities-and-rise-of-stem&#34;&gt;The Decline of the Humanities and Rise of STEM
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In modern society, there is a prevailing societal pressure to choose a STEM major as it is considered the pathway to a fruitful and profitable career, while interest in the seemingly unprofitable humanities field has drastically declined. At Ohio State University, between 2012 and 2020, the number of humanities major graduates dropped by 46%;  at Tufts University, the same number fell by 50%, while at the State University of New York, the decline was almost 75%. (Greenfield) As The Atlantic notes, students “have shifted their view of what they should be studying,” instead of what they want to study “in a largely misguided effort to enhance their chances on the job market” (Schmidt). While the trend of increasing majors in STEM fields may appear to be recent, in fact, this represents a historical trend, with origins at least as far back as 1957, when the Soviet satellite Sputnik 1 was launched (Powell). Since then, we have witnessed the increasing centrality of science and technology to business and our lives on the whole. As a result, “the more favoured disciplines in business and technology bask in the admiration of society and thereby attract funding for studies, research and community engagements,” while, in contrast, “the humanities struggle” (Ikpe).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given the supposed significance of STEM for national competitiveness, government funding incentives and policy actions are employed to promote STEM education. Kentucky Governor Matt Bevin advocated for state colleges and universities to produce more electrical engineers and fewer French literature scholars by withholding funds for schools that encouraged and produced humanities majors (Beam). Similarly, the Obama administration suggested rating the country’s 7,000 colleges and universities in relation to post-graduation earnings, in hopes of encouraging students to choose “useful” and remunerative majors (Anderson).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Given the heavy subsidization of STEM fields by the public sector, can we fairly accuse students’ educational decisions as being anything less than rational? Financial support for and societal encouragement of STEM studies have swayed student opinion greatly, and the majority of youths simply accept the manufactured belief that STEM is always more profitable and benefits society more than the humanities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;scientism-and-the-deification-of-utility&#34;&gt;Scientism and the Deification of Utility
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decline of the humanities in education can be attributed to scientism, the view that science alone can render the truth about the world and reality. STEM has been raised to a degree of quasi-worship since the time of the 16th century Scientific Revolution. Forsaking the supposedly subjective and speculative ideas of the humanities in favor of the seemingly concrete and objective truths about the world inferred via science, people began to see STEM as “useful,” or, more often, profitable. As such,  STEM subjects came to be idealised as “eternal” and “illuminating,” surpassing the limitations of human thought and providing us insight into the universe itself. Many recent examples show that this mindset still pervades. These days, many believe that AI can solve any and all problems, for example, based on the fact that computers can hold many more points of data than humans can and that computers can make empirical discoveries of the world that we cannot understand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet, we not only desire to harness technology, but also fear technology (Rini). As our advances in science and technology reveal to us our prior ignorance and ineptitudes, we respond by trying to accelerate our understanding; in doing so, our fears subsume our judgment. One can see this process in European society’s initial reception to Darwin’s theory of evolution. As existential uncertainty grew in the face of undermined faith, people began to attempt to harness and control that which they feared in the form of eugenics (Rini). The negative effects of this movement are still affecting society today in gene editing projects relying on CRISPR, which, while inspired by our fear of  disease and desire for evolutionary fitness, may lead to our ultimate demise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;efficiency-utility-and-the-ills-of-digital-taylorism&#34;&gt;Efficiency, Utility, and the Ills of Digital Taylorism
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When driven primarily by fear and anxiety, the pursuit of scientific and technological advancement can lead to ethical dilemmas. Heidegger noted that we humans are headed towards simply being a “standing reserve” of supplies meant to be “ordered and conscripted, assembled and disassembled, set up and set aside” (Blitz).  One can see this at work  in the rise of the gig economy, in which workers are devalued as humans and subject to the whims of opaque, data-driven algorithms that reduce workers to  star and numerical ratings (Gandini). Those who do meet the standard—through stars and numbers—are effectively culled. In this phenomenon, known as Digital Taylorism, employers collect detailed, digital data on their employees and automate the system of promoting or firing their workers, while diminishing the value of each individual worker through increasingly streamlined tasks (The Economist).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although productivity and efficiency sound appealing at the outset, the perils of Digital Taylorism and algorithmic management are evident in the treatment of gig workers, whose  “labour power [is turned] into a commodity&amp;quot; (Gandini). Due to the opaqueness of  algorithmic management, workers have little recourse when an algorithm deems them no longer employable. Gig work platforms take little to no responsibility for poor consumer experiences, instead placing the entire blame on the worker, in a “radical responsibilization of the work-force” on the individual level (Fleming).  Workers are seen in the same way that some might view a piece of unresponsive hardware and just as replaceable as a piece of machinery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This instrumental view of humans extends to our fear of AI replacement. AI, for instance, could be more efficient and cost-effective than human labour. As a result, the additional wealth generated through lower labor inputs could lead to an “age of leisure,” as Keynes optimistically predicted in 1930 (Müller). However, our fear of being replaced by AI betrays a widespread, yet unspoken, assumption that humans are merely “instruments” on the same level of AI. Instead of treating technology as a tool to benefit humanity, we have allowed it to instrumentalize and dehumanize us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-humanities-role-in-counteracting-technological-instrumentalism&#34;&gt;The Humanities’ Role in Counteracting Technological Instrumentalism
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of being “raw material for technical operations&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; or the passive recipients of technological benefits, humans should be regarded as active agents who have the ability to shape the course of technological development. Humanities is crucial to guiding the ethical advancement of STEM, and one such example is in tackling bias in AI. AI often reproduces our unconscious biases, and journalist Julia Angwin proved just that in uncovering COMPAS, an AI tool used to predict recidivism in Broward County, Florida. Predictive recidivism tools use metrics such as address, socioeconomic status, and gender to predict future recidivism rates. However, due to existing racism in policing, black victims abound in cases of wrongful arrests.  This skewed data may have caused the discrepancy Julia Angwin discovered in COMPAS’s output, with the tool incorrectly labeling African-American defendants as “high-risk” at nearly twice the rate of white defendants. Although COMPAS is still being used today, the humanities allow us to develop the critical thinking skills necessary to question the implications and consequences of new technologies, and allow us to pinpoint the technologies that may cause more harm than good in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, the humanities can help us create a value system that affirms rather than instrumentalizes human life. By exploring themes of dehumanization, literature allows us to question and pinpoint existing denials of autonomy and personhood. This is perhaps most evident in Kafka’s work, such as his book The Metamorphosis, which explores and uncovers the impossibility of finding meaning within instrumentalism. While society claims that we will find meaning in our work and careers by creating things of value, Kafka’s protagonist Gregor’s job seems to be a dehumanizing place rather than a creator of meaning. He and his coworkers are “tool[s] of the boss, without brains or backbone,” merely an object to be used and discarded, even less human than the insect he was slowly turning into (Kafka). A more modern example may be Kazuo Ishiguro&amp;rsquo;s novel &amp;ldquo;Never Let Me Go,&amp;rdquo; in which the characters, including the protagonist Kathy, are trapped within a society that treats them as commodities, cloned specifically for the purpose of organ donation. Their identities are reduced to the purpose they serve, devoid of any individual agency or autonomy. This dystopian world demonstrates the dehumanizing consequences of technology when it is wielded without ethical consideration, and causes us to reflect on our own desired interpretation of humanity: as inherently meaningful individuals or as extrinsically useful commodities. However, even in these dehumanizing circumstances, both Gregor and Kathy manage to find inherent meaning in their lives, whether it be Gregor’s continued fascination with music and art, or Kathy’s connection to other people, and her desire to be loved and accepted. These, and many other pieces of art, aid us in discovering meaning in a world that does not view us as inherently meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study of the humanities enable humans to demystify the opaque blackbox of technology, guide us in the development of critical thinking skills, and allow us to spend time considering who we are, what we wish to achieve, what sort of life we want to live, and how to derive meaning for ourselves. By studying the humanities, we can gain insights into our own humanity, and work towards a future where technology truly serves as merely a useful tool to shape society, not as a dehumanizing power. The humanities attempt to affirm, or at least help us to discover, meaning, in contrast to a technology-focused society that seeks to instrumentalize us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The societal pressure to prioritize STEM subjects over humanities may stem from an idealization and fear of the sciences, but it has now allowed technology to further dehumanize us. While STEM education can be useful in many ways, the humanities is needed for its ability to foster critical thinking and moral judgment. If technology can bring us progress, then the humanities are needed to make sure we are progressing to a better world, and a balanced education that incorporates both STEM and humanities disciplines is essential to do just that; to utilise technology safely and ethically, and shape ourselves and our societies in a healthy and meaningful manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;bibliography&#34;&gt;Bibliography
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anderson, Nick. “How Much Do Alumni from a College Earn? The Feds Give Answers.” Washington Post, 27 Oct. 2021. &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.washingtonpost.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/grade-point/wp/2015/09/12/how-much-do-graduates-from-a-college-earn-the-federal-government-give-answers/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/grade-point/wp/2015/09/12/how-much-do-graduates-from-a-college-earn-the-federal-government-give-answers/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beam, Adam. Bevin: Ky. Needs Engineers, Not Lit Majors. &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.wcpo.com/news/political/kentucky-state-government-news/bevin-calls-for-kentucky-colleges-to-turn-out-more-electrial-engineers-fewer-french-lit-scholars&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.wcpo.com/news/political/kentucky-state-government-news/bevin-calls-for-kentucky-colleges-to-turn-out-more-electrial-engineers-fewer-french-lit-scholars&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed 9 July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blitz, Mark. “Understanding Heidegger on Technology.” The New Atlantis, no. 41, 2014, pp. 63–80.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Digital Taylorism.” The Economist. The Economist, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.economist.com/business/2015/09/10/digital-taylorism&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.economist.com/business/2015/09/10/digital-taylorism&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed 9 July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fleming, Peter. “The Human Capital Hoax: Work, Debt and Insecurity in the Era of Uberization.” Organization Studies, vol. 38, no. 5, May 2017, pp. 691–709. SAGE Journals, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1177/0170840616686129&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://doi.org/10.1177/0170840616686129&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gandini, Alessandro. “Labour Process Theory and the Gig Economy.” Human Relations, vol. 72, no. 6, June 2019, pp. 1039–56. DOI.org (Crossref), &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1177/0018726718790002&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://doi.org/10.1177/0018726718790002&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greenfield, Nathan M. “The Crisis in Arts and Humanities: Rhetoric or Reality?” University World News, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.universityworldnews.com/post.php?story=20230331111300644&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.universityworldnews.com/post.php?story=20230331111300644&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed 9 July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ikpe, Ibanga B. “The Decline of the Humanities and the Decline of Society.” Theoria: A Journal of Social and Political Theory, vol. 62, no. 142, 2015. PhilPapers,&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.3167/th.2015.6214203&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.3167/th.2015.6214203&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://doi.org/10.3167/th.2015.6214203&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ishiguro, Kazuo. Never Let Me Go. Faber &amp;amp; Faber, 2010.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kafka, Franz. Metamorphosis. Penguin Classics, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Müller, Vincent C. “Ethics of Artificial Intelligence and Robotics.” The Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy, edited by Edward N. Zalta, Summer 2021, Metaphysics Research Lab, Stanford University, 2021. Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://plato.stanford.edu/archives/sum2021/entries/ethics-ai/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://plato.stanford.edu/archives/sum2021/entries/ethics-ai/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Office, Alvin Powell Harvard News. “How Sputnik Changed U.S. Education.” Harvard Gazette, 11 Oct. 2007, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2007/10/how-sputnik-changed-u-s-education/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2007/10/how-sputnik-changed-u-s-education/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rini, Regina. “The Trauma Echo: Science and Public Uncertainty in the Data Century.” Wellesley College Philosophy Colloquium, Nov 2022. Presentation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Schmidt, Benjamin. “Should I Major in the Humanities? - The Atlantic.” The Atlantic, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/08/the-humanities-face-a-crisisof-confidence/567565/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2018/08/the-humanities-face-a-crisisof-confidence/567565/&lt;/a&gt;. Accessed 9 July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2023 Queen&#39;s Commonwealth Competition: Bronze Medal</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2023-queens-commonwealth-competition-bronze-medal/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 06:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2023-queens-commonwealth-competition-bronze-medal/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Freya&amp;rsquo;s Commonwealth Essay - Junior 2023&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Jiaying!&amp;rdquo; She whispered,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uncomfortably restrained, she squirmed,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I distributed the cards with written-on roles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What is it?&amp;rdquo; I replied,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorting Lego-blocks, warriors in disguise,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ready to save a kingdom under siege.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The monsters are approaching!&amp;rdquo; She declared,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her hands animated, battling imaginary foes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I armed my warrior with a strawberry-topped Pocky sword,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preparing for the impending war.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Stand by my side,&amp;rdquo; I whispered softly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Always,&amp;rdquo; came the faithful reply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hours passed as these plays continued,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until exhaustion claimed us, clutching our warriors tight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the car window, a magical world unfurled,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the eyes of a child, dreams knew no bounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lifeless Lego became the start of grand tales,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Childish hands shaping clay-like realms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In those wild worlds, anything was possible,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Princesses fled, monsters revived,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet amidst ever-changing stories, hope remained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We rallied together, facing spontaneous challenges,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fighting courageously whatever came up,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The superpower of imagination to shape a collectively desired world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But as I have grown older, battle cards are no longer an interest,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And with them, the lenses of childhood&amp;rsquo;s view have cracked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The car windows fogged,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The magical world is hidden,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet no castles outside, only shackles in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world, unlike fairy tales, reveals its unfairness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These monsters are no longer visible,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ones that even the strongest sword cannot slay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A division disrupting harmony and determining one’s fate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Colorful realms washed away by furious waves of reality,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Replaced with broken shackles, blown by the wind,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leaving many with hopelessness, left to struggle alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dreams were shattered along with solace,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leaving a lingering sense of dread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything remained, as it was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But hidden monsters attacked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These “warriors” vanished,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Replaced by indifferent stares,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ignoring these pleas for help,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Followed by silent disappearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crowds of indifference,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enforced by adults who believe the world is already stained by unfairness,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Believing in human nature’s inherent evilness,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And thus, nothing could be changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those beliefs enforced societal barriers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ignorant nature of humanity overwhelmed,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turning a blind eye to the symphonies of pleas,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oblivious to the power within us to shape a better world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet, hidden within the hearts of the youth,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A flicker of hope remains, different from this indifferent world,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A superpower awaits reawakening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are practiced at fighting monsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ability to craft a desired world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With visions, a fairy tale world appears,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Absent of prejudice and inequality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A world where creed and color vanish,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boundaries and barriers dissolve into air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Empowered by enterprises,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The youthful superpower rewinds,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The desire to call upon solidarity,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the power to imagine one’s own world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are practiced at facing what we fear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only then, the chains of the past break–&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The normalized ignorance and hatred,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cloudy eyes defog,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And known horrors fade,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the terrible vastness of the possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prejudice crumbles,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shattered by love and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The elders&amp;rsquo; shackles of unfairness shatter,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Replaced with kindness and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The youth, together armed with imagination,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set out to destroy the status quo,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And we practice against monsters,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until a desired world comes true&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Where everyone stands on equal ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although there are still no fairy tales,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No princess or magic to save the day;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our practice stays with us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No warrior fights off these monsters&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except now, wielding the mighty sword of words.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing with all their might,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To break free from the intergenerational shackles,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To disrupt the never-ending loop of inequality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Called upon action,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The words of these youths transform into a power,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calling for solidarity and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unity to construct a new world,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built upon the dreams of the youth,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the practice of vanquishing monsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No longer will humanity turn a blind eye,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For they recognize their collective power to shape the world they desire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And as they craft their own world,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People believe once again in change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With each word written,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each action taken,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They propel themselves forward,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crafting a path to a society free of bias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The power to transform lies within each and every youth,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Waiting to be awakened, to break free from this world&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a pen, and imagination,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Begins the superpower to forge a better future for all.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>The Right People in the Right Places: Changing Police Practices</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/the-right-people-in-the-right-places-changing-police-practices/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/the-right-people-in-the-right-places-changing-police-practices/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Gemma, it’s time for bed. Have you brushed your teeth?” Grandma said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I did, but Grandma, before I go to bed, can I tell you about something that happened at school?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure!” Grandma said, sitting on the edge of Gemma’s bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We had a new teacher today. She doesn&amp;rsquo;t know what she’s talking about!” Gemma stuttered angrily. “Today, we discussed The Giver and she hasn’t even read it and knows absolutely nothing about it. When I tried to tell her that her account of events differed from the book, she immediately denied it, yelled at me, and told me not to speak anymore during the class!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“That doesn’t sound like a good teacher.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What can I do Grandma? It’s the worst class.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grandma thought for a while before she spoke. “In my day, we had terrible schools too. We had many debates about what were called residential schools. Teachers would try to control the kids in order to make them forget their culture. Many think that, “Oh! Those problems are in the past!&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; However, sadly it’s not the case. It isn’t exactly the same, but racism continues to this day, with indigenous voting booths being farther away than others, or news of an indigenous grandfather being arrested by police for simply trying to open a bank account for his granddaughter with his government issued Indian status card.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The police shut down the voices of people who spoke up about injustice. It’s ostensibly the job of the police to ensure citizens obey laws that provide safety and fairness. Instead, they are discriminating against those that speak out and in some cases unknowingly perpetuating systemic racism. Nowadays, after the public execution of George Floyd, there has been a similar movement for defunding the police.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve heard of George Floyd, and it’s awful what happened to him, but how would defunding the police change anything?” Gemma said curiously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, defunding the police is a movement that supports taking away funds from the police and instead using it on non-policing forms of public support and safety such as housing, employment, community health, education and much more. To better understand, there is one person in particular that started this movement, Kandace Montgomery.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I never heard of Kandace Montgomery?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Despite having a disadvantage, she spoke up and potentially opened a new door to a better society. Rightly, she believes the police are asked to solve too many issues that they are not professionally trained for. Instead of police funds going to crimes or prisons which commonly assume that certain races are criminal and perpetuating systemic racism, they can use community social members to do the same thing but possibly with more justice.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Then why not just train the police more? If they can’t do their job properly, make them practice more!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you think it would help if your teacher practiced more and made more detailed lesson plans before class?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course! If she had bothered to read the book, maybe we would even be able to have a proper discussion in class!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sure, it may improve your individual classroom experience, but these problems will only repeat itself, in other classrooms, for other students, as long as your school’s substitute teacher program doesn’t change. Sometimes, problems aren’t individual, but systematic. Retraining police may solve the problem of individual bigoted police officers, but it wouldn’t change an inequitable and violent system. Canada spends significantly less on social services than police services in its national communities. With all that money invested in prisons and policing, it does not make our society safer but on the contrary, more unjust and dangerous. There have already been many attempts to modify the police system from adding more people of all races in the system to the changes after the George Floyd execution. However, none of them worked. The only way to stop violence committed to communities of colour is to defund, not reform.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But Grandma, what does reform have to do with me and my classmates? And what can we do?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, change can start with advocating.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Advo-what?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Advocating can start when you spread the message to your classmates, or start supporting petitions online. For example, when I was your age, the school lunches were awfully cold. So we started a small petition for warmer, more nutritious lunches, and we tried to get everyone in our class to sign it. It worked and in the end, since our school was quite small, the school decided to buy a microwave and change the cafeteria menu.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well, the food in our cafeteria is delicious already. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about that! But what does this have to do with defunding the police and dealing with this bad teacher?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The process starts with speaking to people, gaining support for your cause, starting petitions, joining protests, and educating those that don’t know. Then, you can try to get support from your community, like other students, parents, and teachers. Once you have a movement and support, take it to the principal. Talking to your friends and other students comes first, and parents and grandparents, too!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Okay, get me my phone!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No, no, Gemma. Sleep. You need your strength for tomorrow.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A-sparkle</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/a-sparkle/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/a-sparkle/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A sparkle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Covid lockdown has taken from us and has made us miss significant parts of our lives. Ultimately, we miss our friends and family most, and I am no different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My teacher and classmates, their humor, the sound of chalk scraping against the blackboards, the chatter that almost never stops, these are the moments I miss. On rainy days, my friends and I would run through the heavy rain; hiding under a single rain jacket. On sunny days, we would sunbathe together, rolling down the grassy hills. I remember one such sunny day. We had to run a lap test. Lap tests are short races where the teacher records the time we take to run around the school. I’m not a fast runner&amp;ndash;I grow tired very easily. When I run too much, my stomach aches. You can imagine I’m not a huge fan of lap tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ayma, my best friend at school isn’t tall but all the strongest boys are scared of her. I witnessed her win a race against the fastest boy in our class!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before we started, Ayma turned to me, her eyes sparkling. She held my hand in hers and promised that she would run with me, whispering, “Bring me chocolate tomorrow.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I laughed and nodded along as her eyes caught the light from the sun, and I felt its warmth between us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all started together. I ran as fast as I could while Ayma jogged easily beside me. I sped up, staying with the others, not wanting to drag Ayma down. I sped up, and she was still by my side, laughing&amp;ndash;her eyes sparkling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a moment, it felt as if the world was only the two of us. We made jokes, laughing all of our worries away. Even the soft wind tickled, making me laugh even harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I completely forgot about the teacher who was timing us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But my stomach began to ache. Soon I began to slow down. I shut my eyes in pain, but Ayma was still by my side. The entire time, I thought I could never ever have a better friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven’t seen Ayma for about a year now. The last time was over half a year ago. I learned that eyes don’t sparkle as much through a glass screen, or maybe it is running with a best friend that makes eyes brighter. I miss the moments and the sparkles and sounds of spending time together; even when feeling pain I still miss seeing and hearing my best friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Spring, the cherry blossoms bloomed and my sister Alice and I walked outside. We smelled the fresh air in the streets near our home. Heart-like petals flew off the trees and fluffy squirrels hopped everywhere, running and laughing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I laughed and thought of Ayma. I began to run ahead of Alice, but I realized I only heard my footsteps. I turned around, wondering what was going on, and she was barely moving!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was drifting through the petals around her and only pausing to look at her phone. She started walking a few steps forward, then she stopped again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Come on!” I shouted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alice didn’t understand what was going on but she followed me. The sun was burning that day and I ran and she caught up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although we have lived for years beside the same shops, it felt like I hadn’t been in this neighbourhood before. The details had changed. Shops had closed, others had new signs of Covid, and the people were unidentifiable under their masks. I hadn’t walked on the sidewalk for a long time, and I had forgotten the feel, but I would never forget the smell of bread from inside the bakeries, and was thankful some of the stores that hadn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years were the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I craved ice cream, but in the end, the ice cream ended up dripping all over my new shirt, and I was shocked how fast time flew. It was the most fun I’d had during the long quarantine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although, lives have changed: people might have not seen their families for a long time, some people might be facing economic problems, and some might have lost their loved ones. Despite not knowing what might happen in the future, I believe that we should all have hope that we will reunite again, and the sparkles and sounds and feelings that we have been missing will come back from behind the glass, like people in our lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/image_0.gif&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2021，四月散记</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2021%E5%9B%9B%E6%9C%88%E6%95%A3%E8%AE%B0/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 11:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2021%E5%9B%9B%E6%9C%88%E6%95%A3%E8%AE%B0/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;写作业&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近，多了n个作业。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比如阅读作业，词汇作业，数学。最烦的就是，这些课的老师都是中国老师&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;每一次都几章的发，不像那些外国老师每次作业就是两道题。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;唔，要开始写作业了，我安静了下来，挺的相当直，用自信的眼神瞪着电脑。一打开文档，感觉作业也没太多。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;拿起数学就开始晃笔， 把在阅读课上从不用的技巧用到了数学上。不会做就先读题！还不会这么办？继续读题！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看到了一道很荒谬的题，“小明在解一个方程，但是他不小心把X看成负的了。请问这个方程的正确答案是什么？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;突然想起我妈妈的话，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”在国外这种考试总共三道题。粗心一下，扣0.5分。一分一分就这样扣没的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;想起了这句话，我就开始觉察到自己内心的愤怒和无能感。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;过了一会，我叹了口气，跟自己说，”反正数学也没怎么重要，还是先写会日记吧。“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;刚坐下来，背自动的一点一点往下垂，脚一点一点往上抬。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后，电脑到了肚子上，左腿到了桌子上，左腿高高在上的看着在下面的右脚。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;此时，我懂得了爸爸。。。。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;打开一个新文档就正正花了五分钟，刚开头就卡住了，写来写去也绕不过 “最近。。。“这两个字。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我又跟自己说，”反正日记也没怎么重要” 抬头看了看闹钟&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;感觉自己好伟大，一下子就做了一个小时的作业。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这么努力的孩子这时候是应该歇会了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2021.4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;成长中的人性&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;人长大，按道理来说是应该情感上，理解上，智商上都更加成熟了，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是反而现在的的小孩的行为比幼儿园的孩子还古怪。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比如现在小小孩喜欢，白雪公主，狮子王，英雄类的人物等等&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;长大一两岁，喜欢的就是跟自己有共情的人物。比如白雪公主养的那只胖老鼠，狮子王里面的野猪等等。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;再长大一两岁，喜欢的不管是人物，还是东西变的越来越邪恶。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;孩子可以随便从你的兜掏你的东西，可以摔你的东西但是自己会先开始哇哇大哭。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这种行为能用什么词形容？单纯？幼稚？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;不，这就是无意识下的恶毒。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;很多小孩都读过个寓言，“狐狸与葡萄”；&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;故事就是讲一个狐狸，看到一棵葡萄树。想吃树上的葡萄但是自己够不到。。就告诉了其他小动物葡萄是酸的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;从中医的阴阳五行来说，狐狸显然是个太阴之人。自己还没到能阻止别人能吃这个葡萄，只是自己吃不到也不想让别人吃到。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;讲了这么多，还是cynthia的一句话点醒了我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我，本人，竟然也还是个孩子。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>MyAntonia</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/myantonia/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 13:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/myantonia/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My Antonia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story starts in the 1800s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jim Burden went aboard a train to Virginia to live with his grandparents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time flew by, he quickly adapted to his new home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He got a warm home with his loving grandparents, Peter and Parel, his new friends, and Antonia as his student&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jim and Antonia played all day. Together, they discovered new adventure areas, made pastries together while Jim also helped Antonia with her studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Jim’s help, Antonia has adapted to this new land while her long-lasting friendship with Jim began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jim was attracted to the bright personality of Antonia and the light atmosphere from being around her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One thing Jim disliked about Antonia was that Antonia was behaving inferior to him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once, the children borrowed a knife from Peter and went on a prairie trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When messing around, they were approached by a rattlesnake while Jim and Antonia were so focused that they did not realize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the snake was striking, Jim turned around and stabbed the snake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antonia bragged about the &amp;ldquo;Courageous&amp;rdquo; behavior of and how manly he was while killing the snake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antonia never acted inferior to Jim again while Jim got the little respect he wanted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, Parel died suddenly. In shock, Peter starts looking for a new job to support the family while Mr. Shimerada is jealous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon they realized they could barely support the family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During winter, Jim had a cozy warm holiday with his grandparents while Mr. Shimerada has awful financial issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During January, Jim’s grandparents invited Mr.Shimerada over.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While witnessing how Jim has been living so comfortably, Mr. Shimerada regretted his decision of moving over here, while he still hasn’t moved on from Peter’s death. And so, he committed suicide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The family experienced another family member&amp;rsquo;s death, the whole family has been more distant, including Jim and Antonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Around March, Antonia joined her brother with farm work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Antonia no longer had time to play with Jim all day long like before, soon they distanced away for the second time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few years, Jim’s grandparents and he moved away from Virginia for Jim to have better education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Jim was studying, Antonia was working with a cutter. During their free time, they would go and dance together at clubs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jim still had feelings for Antonia however Antonia only had feelings for him as a little brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few years, Jim and Antonia left each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, Jim overheard from Lina that Antonia got married, however, he didn’t visit her until he received a letter from Antonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was one thing that caught Jim’s eye especially, it was the letter signed as, Your old friend, Antonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When he visited Antonia at the farm, they both changed so much, they barely recognized each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had hands rough from working at the farm, and quite a few cheerful children but still the cheerful personality that he missed dearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remembering all the moments from their childhood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favorite character is Antonia, her overall personality seems like a joyful dainty girl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a girl hiding behind Jim’s back, she slowly grew into an independent woman with her own thoughts and decisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After emigrating multiple times, she no longer had anyone to depend on, enduring so much burden and still being the same joyful girl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the story, she represents all the memories and love of Jim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this book since even though the book didn’t end in the stereotypical happy ending, i still feel like it’s a happy ending for both of them. With jim overcoming his past, and Antonia with her new future.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>MobyDick</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/mobydick/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 01:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/mobydick/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moby Dick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ishmael, a sailor arrives at New Bedford where he met several friends. One named QueeQueq, with whom he shared a bed. At first, he seemed intimidating but after several encounters, eventually, Ishmael saw the nice side of him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, they went to Nantucket to start a voyage on a ship named Pequord, with a strange captain named Ahab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after the Pequord took sail, Ahab made his first appearance on the ship, announcing how his leg broke by a whale named Moby Dick and declaring his desire to seek vengeance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moby Dick however wasn’t an ordinary whale, barely anyone knows much about him except the fact that he was a legendary white whale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sailors soon set on their mission to capture Moby Dick, they captured a few whales, but they caught no sign of Moby Dick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some unlucky phonetics came true too, several misfortunes almost led to death, including a little boy who barely survived after being left behind, also a harpooner almost sank but got rescued by QueeQueq.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, a typhoon lit the ship on fire, the crew members luckily survived. Just by a few days, a sailor drowned by falling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crew member’s soon realized the mission they’re going on is practically “suicidal” which led to a rival towards Ahad to return home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Ahad did not listen to the members, but his anger towards the whale started to exaggerate hearing how his friends could not endure with him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His desire to find the halo exaggerated, his anger continued to rise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After days of hunting, they finally found Moby Dick. They became their intensive attack, with Ahad caught in the harpoon and swirled to death. With Ishmael flung out from the earlier attack, he was the only survivor of this disaster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He went aboard another ship, where he continued to search for dead members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t think there is a certain amiable character in this story, so I guess my least favorite character is Ahad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ahad has lost his foot to the whale, which I’m sure that the whale didn’t target him unlike he did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is allowed to get furious as it is an incurable injury. However, he got swirled inside his hate for the whale and pulled an entire crew of people to get swirled in his feelings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think this was a selfish behavior, however, despite how he couldn’t be rational during that period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this book for an adventure fiction story, the plot is interesting and the point of the characters was clear. The madness and tribulation were foreshadowing every movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And i found online that many of the characters had interpretations. Such as Ahab representing an evil king leading the Israelites into doom; Rachel (the ship that saved Ishmael) was representing the mother of Joseph, known for protecting her children.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>PrideandPrejudice</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/prideandprejudice/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 04:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/prideandprejudice/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pride and Prejudice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bennet family had five sisters, all with their own charm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mrs. Bennet was eager to see all her daughters married due to the daughters&amp;rsquo; age and inheritance problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a while, soon the news got spread around of a rich gentleman, Mr. Bingley, arriving with his friend named Mr. Darcy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon the arrival of a  wealthy gentleman named Mr. Bingley, he joined a local ball in the neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He spent the whole evening at the ball, dancing, while he took an interest in the eldest daughter of the Bennet family, Jane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Mr. Darcy was not very sociable, he rejected everyone at the ball which made his reputation in the neighborhood awful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the ball ended, the family was excited about Mr. Bingley’s interest in Jane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jane commented about Mr. Bingley’s charming behavior and amiable personality while Mr. Bingley also liked her back thinking that she was the “Prettiest” among them despite their difference in social status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After several other social gatherings, Mr. Darcy started to show attraction towards Elizabeth, however, he thought of her as “not fit for a wife”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After Elizabeth came over to the Netherlands, their relationship got to the point that Mr. Bingley noticed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few months passed, just when Elizabeth left Neverland, Elizabeth found out that her best friend got married to Mr. Collins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mr. Collins was a foolish guy, not even to mention he just got rejected by Elizabeth a few months ago. Her friend explained that she did not marry Mr. Collin by love, she needed financial support and her parents were rushing her marriage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearing of her friend’s situation, Elizabeth had a goal to marry by happiness and will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jane visited the town to meet friends, but she secretly wished to meet Mr. Bingley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Jane got a sudden proposal from Mr. Darcy, which she respectfully rejected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after, she received another letter from Mr. Darcy, in which he apologized for forbidding her sister&amp;rsquo;s engagement, but he insists that Jane and Mr. Bingley aren&amp;rsquo;t a serious couple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During Spring, Lydia came back to the Netherlands married to a man named Mr. Wickham.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jane also got a proposal from Mr. Bingley, Jane was delighted and accepted the proposal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A relative of Mr. Darcy forbids Elizabeth to accept Darcy’s feelings, Elizabeth said that she does not want to get married to Mr. Darcy, but she wants to marry against her will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon Mr. Darcy proposed to Elizabeth, Elizabeth accepted happily which resulted in a happy ever after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favorite character is Elizabeth, for I think she’s a quick-witted girl with also an amiable personality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was one who got a happier ending in this story, I guess how she insisted on marrying for love and nothing else paid off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elizabeth was also a good sister, she had good relationships with her sisters, she always comforted them when they were sad and talked together all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think she has self-realization skills which are pretty admirable, she realized her prejudice against him and overcame it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this book since the dialogues and details in this story made the story very interesting and vivid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of the characters was written as the antagonist, though some of them made decisions that were incorrect from a reader’s perspective, instead were fairly from a character’s perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I do think that some characters were written selfishly but still ended in a neverless happy ending.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2021年2月中文日记</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2021%E5%B9%B42%E6%9C%88%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 14:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2021%E5%B9%B42%E6%9C%88%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近疫情的关系，大人小孩都呆在家，出不去，小孩只能在网上上课，大人只能网上上班。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当然，我还是蛮开心，网上上课比现场上课容易很多，而且时间又短。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是也难免有一些尴尬的事情发生，会是什么呢？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;上周五，学校网上上课的时候，当时我已经一动不动的坐了一个小时了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;熬呀熬，勉强又坐了十分钟，实在无聊了，对着天空翻了个白眼，刚好老师点倒我的名字了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;老天可能都没注意到这种表情的无意识运动，但是摄像头咔嚓一下记录下来了，屏幕卡住了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;正好老师注意到了我，同学注意到了，天啊，全世界都注意到了，那张大屏幕上的鬼脸！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这时候已经不可能跳回一个小时前，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我在无奈之下，只能一遍一遍安慰自己，保持一个平静的样子并且希望“全世界”今天心情好。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;下课后，还有更可怕的，就是同班同学。当面会笑眯眯的看着你，放学后朋友发了条短信说，“全班刚才都笑死了”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;出丑的反义词是什么？按谷歌的话就是“争光”，按孩子的话来说就是现在流行的“酷”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;怎么避免这些“尴尬”的事情呢?怎么争光呢？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比如老师在上面讲你在下面讲，抢答抢到你举了手老师都不点你。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;虽然我以上的事情都没在我身上发生过，“争光”我不会，但是我会“打光”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我的同学有些头上照着蓝光，红光，黄光，甚至黑光看都看不见。而我，像天使下凡似的，身边围着神圣之光，脸上照的闪闪发光。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我最后总结出来了一个完美的上网课的方案；头一定要比桌子低，为了避免老师看到不断的哈欠；不能使摄像头拍到嘴但是必须得拍到眼睛，为了让老师知道这个学生还在。电脑保持倾斜，心里保持敞亮。到哪里也难免有一些尴尬的事情发生，如果不能光明正大的面对，那就象我这样，用神一般的情商和智商来解决。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>中文议论文：解析第一性原理</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AE%AE%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87%E8%A7%A3%E6%9E%90%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%80%A7%E5%8E%9F%E7%90%86/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 04:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AE%AE%E8%AE%BA%E6%96%87%E8%A7%A3%E6%9E%90%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%80%A7%E5%8E%9F%E7%90%86/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;解析第一性原理&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第一性原理就是解决世间万物，任何问题中的本质和底层代码。 熟悉运用第一性原理的分析方法，可以帮助人们分解所有的问题，而能够更轻松地，同时高效率的解决问题。在任何情况下，找到问题的第一性原理都是重要的，能让问题的本质呈现，就能高效率的简化，处理，最终解决成一个满意的结果。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;下面分析一下什么是第一性原理；&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;首先, 像梁冬在“冬吴同学会”里说的那样：“世界观决定世界，人生观决定人生”意思就是，世界的第一性原理就是世界观，对待世界的态度和观念，人生的第一性原理就是人生观，对待人生的态度和观念。详细一点讲，人生观影响着人的价值取向和人生的方向，世界观建立一个人对自然，社会的观念。世界和人生这些听上去是个宏伟的大问题，但第一性原理都是态度和观念，只要抓住了第一性原理，也能够“简化，处理，解决” 这些人生的面对的所有的大事。简单说，我们从小学这么多大道理就是为了建立人生观，世界观，建立处理人生中碰到所有问题的能力。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其次，为什么埃隆·马斯克取得出色的成绩？首先是特斯拉，现在又是火箭， 他是怎么做到的？最主要的是，他抓住了第一性原理并且应用到了他所有想做的事情身上。举个例子；所有人都知道有名的Tesla电动汽车。解决电动汽车可以便宜，可以长时间行驶的第一性原理，就是电池的价格和效率。其他人都认为“电动汽车”，最主要的是汽车的安全性， 因此没有抓住第一性原理也没有得到一个满意的突破。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后，讲讲人生的成功和第一性原理的关系。人要获得成功首先具备两个能力，远见和弹性思维，同时不忘初心走对方向。关于第一性原理的重要部分就是摆脱惯性思维/直线思维，用W思维（WHY思维/曲线思维）来思考问题。如果碰到困难，就应该不停的追问自己第一性原理。简要的说；惯性思维的特征就是，简单粗糙甚至有点洗脑的效果。弹性思维的特征是；试着用其他方法去找解决问题本质。两个思维最大的不一样就是曲线思维会试着去找一件事情的第一性原理。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;上面举了很多例子，但是究竟是怎么找到第一性原理的？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;为了找到第一性原理，得先把表面清理一遍，清理完任何事物当中的不重要的事情后，第一性原理就呈现了，也就是任何问题的本质就出来了。抓住了第一性原理，就能解决。就是梁冬说的要“象佛教那样彻底打破原有思维方式的壁垒”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;同一个问题的第一性原理不是不变的，需求不一样，第一性原理也会不一样。我比姐姐小九岁，据说我我受的中文教育的方式和姐姐的很不同。就是因为妈妈对中文教育的第一性原理的认识改变了。首先讲讲我吧；我呢，首先背了一遍老子的道德经，共81章，虽然一点都不知道每一章是讲什么的，但是勉强的背下来了。后来，又开始读绘本，读完绘本以后，寻找绘本的底层代码。是不是听上去很无聊，但是妈妈感叹，“你看看，你没受过中国的教育的苦但是中文还是不错的”相比姐姐小时候，妈妈每天晚上给她讲故事，甚至讲了三个时的白蛇传。我特别羡慕, 因为妈妈从来没给我讲过故事，更别说三个小时了。在我眼里姐姐受到教育就很好玩，每天晚上都能听故事。不想听，随时停止服务。一个五星级酒店也不会有个这么好的讲故事的服务。我也不是没听过故事，妈妈瞎编的小臭臭的故事每天晚上陪伴了我的成长。妈妈总结下来，“语言的第一性原理是阅读，讲故事的第一性原理是爱”她经常感叹，“你看看，抱着书和抱着孩子本人就是不一样，每天三个小时照着书读故事还比不过一句随口瞎编的小臭臭”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;总结：对任何一件事，要有清醒的分析能力，去抓住它的第一性原理，从而让这件事情清楚地呈现，以便处理，解决，应对。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>中文生活随笔</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E7%94%9F%E6%B4%BB%E9%9A%8F%E7%AC%94/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 02:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E7%94%9F%E6%B4%BB%E9%9A%8F%E7%AC%94/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;2020.12.30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我每天早上十点钟起来，妈妈和爸爸嫌弃我起来太晚了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐某一天十点钟起来了，妈妈和爸爸觉得“太阳从西边出来了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我每天早一点下楼，妈妈和爸爸觉得倒是应该的&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐某一天早一点下楼，爸爸和妈妈都好吃惊&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;是不是很明显的对比？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;某一天姐姐十点钟起来了，爸妈都惊叹是“太阳从西边出来了”。而我当时跟他们的想法是一样的，附和着 “哇塞诶，姐姐，今天你太了不起了，十点钟，这么早就起来了。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是我又仔细的想了想，姐姐，一个二十岁的“大人”。跟个十岁的小孩同时起床，这才是“太阳从西边出来了”,真是好过分. 一个二十岁的“大人应该像爸爸一样五点起来还差不多.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;来，看看一个随意的歇息日；&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“砰 砰 砰” ，中午十二点半，姐姐终于出来了， 身穿花样繁多的睡裙，敞开破袖口，眼如锋利的老鹰一般。呵呵，可能三国演义里会这样写，但是在我的眼中这只是一个还是陷入进白日梦，床头气里的人。眼见着，她来到饭桌旁边，简单吃了几口，把空碗砸到水池里面去，然后就走了。走的时候，爸爸在担心姐姐如此这般怎么适应未来的工作，我担心姐姐如此这般跟着还做不做甜点，妈妈担心如此这般爸爸又来跟她抱怨。而一家人担心的本尊此刻坐在厕所的瓷砖上无忧的歇息。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;一个二十岁的“大人，原来会这样。如此这般，我也对九年后的我，没有伟大的梦想了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20201222&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近我看到我皮肤一直在发，很烦。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;所以我当然去跟我的“闺蜜”散散心，虽然我的“闺蜜”总是不太热情。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我已进姐姐的房间，她就像个老手一样，瞅了我一眼，立马躺下开始让自己的脑子进入歇息状态。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这就是我所说的”不太热情“。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她不理我么，我也得自我娱乐，到她房间东摸西摸，找出来了一瓶白色的油。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我这个人，找到了一个东西，当然得研究清楚，所以我查了一下是什么。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;结果大概是，能让皮肤变白的一种玩意&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我说 “我怎么还不知道你这么在乎你自己的肤色的“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我再说 “这个油。。干嘛用的？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“这个啊，因为我找不到油所以就用这个了“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”你读过上面写着什么么？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”没有呀，写啥了？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”让皮肤变白的“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”没关系的呀，反正都一样的“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”你有没有想过用化妆品“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说，“有啊”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“你几岁开始想过用化妆品的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“唔，我好像十岁的时候特别想要用”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“说说看？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“我当时好像想当一个白老鼠，妈妈还给我用她的眉笔画了胡子“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这瓶变白的油会不会是当时她想当白老鼠时留下的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;20201126&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有一次，我问姐姐哪里买一条裙子。她犹豫了一下，她竟然先找了淘宝。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我当时很吃惊。我姐姐，从来没有在任何购物网站买过任何东西的一个人，更别说淘宝了。怎么会第一个想出来的是淘宝？而且当时，爸爸也已经回到加拿大了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐说，“啊？便宜呀，而且也有更多东西”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我现在觉得姐姐肯定私密下试着在淘宝上买过东西，毕竟她其实喜欢一些东西的，就不买而已。就是不表达出来而已，毕竟爸爸回国的时候姐姐没一次问过爸爸带回任何东西。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐不买东西的原因是，她觉得自己完全没钱。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐明明微信里面存的钱都够买好几杯珍珠奶茶。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有时候，她会意识到自己还是有这把钱的，大概找到自己缺少的那根筋了。会想到给我买珍珠奶茶。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是最近可能因为这个传染病，很多商店生意都不好了。疫情时期外卖点的甜点经常退货，尤其是一家千层蛋糕店。每次点了就退回来，再点，又退回来，每次还补给我们三块钱。最近这家千层蛋糕店倒闭掉了，我还是有点内疚，可能就是因为商家给我们太多三块钱了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是我姐，真是一个拥有着菩萨心肠的人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;每次退货，她就对我说，“唔，没办法，我们下个星期再试着点吧。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这样，商家没倒闭掉，但我的心已经被她“倒闭掉了”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2020.12.10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“姐姐，下来！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;上面传来很小的一声，“嗯”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;过了一个小时，整个屋子一点声音也没有。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;连妈妈打一个嗝，我也会被惊吓到。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;此刻的我心情非常糟糕，没人陪我聊天，没人听完唠叨，无聊死了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近，妈妈一直说姐姐在赶作业，很忙，到二十号才能停。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有时候我会想：她到底有多少作业？她到底有多少作业才会连做蛋糕也不跟我一起做？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;为了解这个问题，我把这个情况换成了一道应用题：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;假设一天，小明能做掉一个作业，那小明二十天能做掉多少作业？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;按逻辑，小明能做掉二十个作业。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是如果换到我姐姐身上，她天天24小时从头到晚没循序在睡觉，我姐姐到底能做掉几个作业呢？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;没人算得出来，但是我们能结论成：比二十少&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我跟姐姐完全不一样，我虽然也能睡很长时间。但只要有几次九点种起来，我的身体也会察觉到九点了，然后就自动的把我脑子也叫醒了。这大概就是妈妈说的，“姐姐少了根筋，我多了根筋吧“。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10.25&amp;mdash;11.1  妈妈闭关&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;才一个月左右，妈妈刚从上次闭关出来。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;本来她打算出关以后，过一个星期就开始另外一次闭关的。后来姐姐考试，妈妈又等了一天又一天。之 后又碰到姐姐选课，然后爸爸又快回来了，她终于等不及了，今天开始闭关一个星期&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第一天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我姐姐是个非常有童年心的一个成人，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;很多事情证明了这一点。比如说：姐姐刚说了一句非常有童年心的一个金句。今天，姐姐上了她所说的“学校的办公时间“，我在旁边的高凳上听但是没听的很清楚，可是我还是听见了姐姐的尴尬的笑声。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;过了一会，老师大概想要姐姐解释一下她不清楚的地方。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐直接说了一个很有深度的例子：“比方说” 然后她会停一停再说 ，“我很喜欢苹果而且苹果也很喜欢我”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后后面又讲了一大堆。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后那个老师都没听清楚，只能猜她大概说了什么。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我觉得姐姐的很细很细的声音很特别。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在她说话的时候，全场所有的人都会停下来，非常努力的听她说话，连珍珠奶茶店的买方都会凑过来听她。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我，就是个非常理性的一个孩子，所有人都知道。虽然有时候还是会有点奇怪：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比如有一次，我找到了一个很大的石头，那块石头长得蛮酷的，但是不知道能用来干什么。我看了一下周围，恍然有灵感了。跑到游乐场旁边的下铺捡了一堆小石头，把自己的裙子当成一个口袋一样，装了进去，跑回了大石头那里。把东西都集在一起后，看了看，但是总是觉得缺了些东西。突然我又看到了一棵很高的树，上面有好多鲜红的果子。但是旁边围满了有刺的叶子。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;树的下面，有几块大石头，叠在一起大概能搞到那些果子。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;折磨了半天，终于我把一堆果子扔下来了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;把材料全集在了一起，用那个大石头砸到那堆小石头上。过了半天，只剩下那个大石头和一堆粉. 我一直认为石头里面总有钻石的。但是砸了一年，也没有找到。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;后来过了几年，我才知道，砸多少石头都不会找出一个钻石的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第二天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐最近发现她以前欺负我的方法没用了，比如把我关在房间外面,关闭我的网页, 挠我痒痒（这个方法还是有点用的）。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;除了这些，她想出来很多，新的，非常奇特的方法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;像迪士尼里面的一个我曾经去过的一个过山车，那个过山车被造成一个恐龙型的U形状，爸爸说这个过上车做了很好的失控的感觉。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有一次，我看到两个伟大的女的为了朋友圈而不在乎自己的危险。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在个过山车上，拿着个手机很勇敢的在自拍，而胆小的我在后面尖叫。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐想出的方法很那个恐龙过上车很类似，姐姐占我体重很轻的便宜，把我抱起来，甩几下，然后就扑通一下蹲下出。最终感觉可能就是爸爸说的 “很好的失控的感觉”吧。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我感觉有一天迪斯尼会招姐姐去，毕竟她3分钟就造出来了一个他们造了几年的一个感觉，而现在我打算期待这一天。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第四天&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;世界上，最可怕的一件事情，就是一个人挠你痒，不管他是故意的还是不小心的。都是一个很可怕的罪行。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有时候，如果我刚听了个笑话，很开心的话，连风吹我，我都会觉得很痒。那种情况，也没办法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是如果一个人，为了让你吃完果汁，把你推到墙的角落然后说，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“暖暖，如果你不把这碗果汁五分钟吃完的话”，然后就做了一个挠痒的手势，看了我一眼就走了。还有一种人，会因为自己的乐趣而挠别人，说笑声是对身体好的，一听就知道那是我妈妈，她还会在我洗澡的时候搓我一边说，“哇塞，你几天没洗你脸了，脏的不得了，你摸摸看！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“你是个女孩子，又不是个脏兮兮的男孩子，女孩子的脸得很白的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后会在每个部位上重复一遍同样的话，只是中间换个词。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这些都没什么，能忍过。但是最可拍的时候就是她上半身全搓完了以后说的那句，“来把脚抬起来“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这句话让我想起了恐怖片里面的坏人把一个人抓起来的时候，“喂你，把你头抬起来”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;后面一个英雄会闯进来把那个人给救了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是浴池里哪里会有什么英雄，只有水声，我，和那个要挠我痒的那个人，我妈妈。我完全不能反抗，过了一阵子，浴室里面发出来了好几声惨叫，那是我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第五天&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“啊，又画歪了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“啊，橘色在那里？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;对面穿过来了好连续的一段惨叫。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;转过身一看，看到姐姐旁边的盘子里，里面放了一个歪的个西瓜，旁边的奶油都漏出来了，。场面看上出像恐怖片里的场面。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;早知道就不应该想出来怎么复杂的主意了。我们本来想做那种蛋糕店门外面摆着的长得像装饰品一样的饼干。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后发现不可能的，总结下来“能做漂亮的饼干的人一定都有巫术“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我们做出来了一堆很难看得饼干，而且也太甜了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是做出来很开心，反正最后也吃不下的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;上次闭关，我本来想的是下次会更好。但是没有，竟然像普通的一天。细思极恐，原来我习惯了！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;现在已经离下次妈妈闭关很远了，也不需要想下次怎么样，活在当下.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9.1&amp;ndash;9.10  妈妈辟谷闭关的十天，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈最近闭关了十天，她早就想着去闭关了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈闭关了，我其实很惨的，剩下的一个家里的人都在折磨我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸会把我的电脑的Wi-Fi给断了，姐姐把我的网页全block掉了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;而且她会用各种方式欺负我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;哼！！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第一天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;吃饭的时候，姐姐只给我了十分钟。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我抱怨说，“不是昨天还二十分钟么，怎么越来越少了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐一点都没在意的加了一句，“一分钟过了，还有三分钟。。。。。。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“不是刚才还有十分钟么？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;吃饭的时候，姐姐只给我了十分钟。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我抱怨说，“不是昨天还二十分钟么，怎么越来越少了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐用我的语气说，”不是昨天还十分钟么，怎么越来越多了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我“哼” 了一声就不理她了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“哼，我就是一个很坏很坏的一个巫婆，你就是那个可怜的被我绑架的公主“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我在旁边叫道，”那我的白马王子在哪里呢？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐似乎没听见的，就坏笑的走了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第三天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;客厅传来一个尖叫，“回来！不然晚上不给你吃面！！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我“哼”了一声，心里想着，“反正昨天晚上已经吃过了，而且今天的汤很难喝”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;过了五分钟，客厅很安静，只听见快速的脚步声。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;又过了几分钟，听到一个叫声，“暖暖！你如果不把蔬菜吃完的话，我会把你按到一个角落里挠你五分钟痒的！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我想了想那残酷的场面，还是回去了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;到最后两分钟，慢慢消失的吃面的机会和残酷的姐姐挠我痒都摆在眼前了。我赶紧拿了一杯水把饭都硬咽下去了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;按姐姐的话说，我到最后两分钟拿了一杯水把菜和饭都硬咽下去了，吞的时候还会用我的可爱的大眼睛看着她，似乎在说，“你看我！这么可怜，你想你的妹妹被呛死么？!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最可恶的是，连外公都支持这种威胁我的方式，说，“姐姐都是为你好”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第五天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我早上一边嚼着寿司一边看了一下我的网页。但是不知道为什么进不去，我看了一下网络，网络很好的。刷新了一下网页，还是没好。我着急的去找姐姐问她究竟干了什么。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“唔，我好像昨天对你生气了，你不听我的话！” 她反过身看了我一眼，“你不昨天问我对你的电脑干了什么么？你现在知道了，开心么？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我回想了一下，想到上次我把姐姐被子藏起来以后，妈妈告诉我，说姐姐把我的网站全block掉了。又想了想昨天晚上我怎么得罪她了，没想起来“我昨天晚上怎么得罪你了？？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她喊，“你不听我的话，哼，叫你大拜，你就不肯”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我又回想了一下，确实有这件事。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第七天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“你觉得这个咸么？妈妈会不让我吃么？我们不能就点个多奶酪的么？“我反复烦她，反复唠叨姐姐，要她今天买个披萨。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐其实也蛮想吃的，毕竟她昨天晚上提过一下的，所以我们就点了一个正常的披萨。可是后来她觉得太咸，然后让我在披萨酱和多奶酪里面选。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我纠结了很久，因为我从来没有看到过一个没有披萨酱的披萨，但是我蛮喜欢吃奶酪的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后我还是点了披萨酱和普通奶酪。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐喊，“暖暖！到十二点了！吃午饭了！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“唔，披萨还没到呢”我很舍不得地到门口看了一下，只看到一个披萨盒坐在角落里，似乎已经呆了很久了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;准备吃的时候，姐姐先把披萨从我手里抢回去说，“我得先吃一口，看看咸不咸”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她咬了一口，皱了一下眉头，一边嚼一边说，“好咸！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我很失望的看着她，平常我这个眼神都有效果的，但是这次竟然没有。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她咬了几口说，”好像是披萨酱咸，不对，是奶酪咸，不对这个披萨就是盐里捞出来的！！“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐像开窍了一样，看了我一眼，用了一个水果刀把整个披萨刮了一遍，然后放在水里搓了几遍，然后整个披萨都变白了，看上出就像一团面团团一样。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐再咬了一口，还是觉得咸，最终没办法了，就给我吃了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第九天：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“我衣服只借给你两天！妈妈闭关完就还给我”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在床头，扔了一件衣服，穿上了，但是一天以后怎么办？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我一起床，慢慢的进她的房间。只是她的门还碍事，一碰就开始“哧哧“的叫，似乎在告诉姐姐有一个人进她房间一样。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;门摇晃了半天，终于安静了，姐姐也没发现我进来了，只翻了一个身然后又继续睡了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;终于，我拿到了一件睡衣。看她了一眼，她在床上睡的可香了，发生了这么多动静，她本事真大。我抱着衣服就跑了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;回去试了一下，发现这件衣服实在是太大了。我再次闯进去，把衣服塞回去，再拿了一件。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最终，我终于有了一件衣服穿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;总而言之，姐姐这次虽然没管住我，但是我还是很感恩姐姐照顾了我，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;虽然她会把我关在房间外面，但是姐姐在这十天里每天都会早晚提醒我所有的事项，比如什么时候上课，什么时候吃饭，什么时候睡觉，她手机的铃声现在还会每天响。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;还有我很感恩她给我买披萨和珍珠奶茶。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;下次，我希望她不会折磨我断我的网，不会给我吃面团团披萨，而且也不会跟我抢衣服穿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;下一次我肯定我也会比这次好，能跟姐姐非常良好的交流。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8.18&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;快开学了，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;一般上学的前两天，我都很有潜力，想着这个学期我一定要做一个好学生，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;特别的挑了一个简单的铅笔盒，在里面塞满了笔。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;非常认真的听课，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;连作业也理的很整齐。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;考试也考的还好，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;下课的时候也会整理书和铅笔盒。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;只是只要过一个星期，我的好心态就不见了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;铅笔盒一塌糊涂，一个活动铅笔能至少少两个零件。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我本来只有一支笔，弹簧没了，橡皮也不见了。 等到一学年差不多要过完的时候，差不多铅笔盒已经被拆空了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;每个星期回家拿一支铅笔，最后家里的铅笔盒也莫名其妙的空了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8.12&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐拿着她的电脑上楼了，过了几分钟, 听到一下“咣当”很大的关门声音。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我追着赶上去，过了一会，没把她弄下来，反而被她踢出来了，还被骂了一句“好烦人“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这是每天都要发生的事情。这一点也不好玩， 这是个悲剧。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我的朋友也有个姐姐，我去请教她该怎么办。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说，“只要她走进你在的房间里，你就走出去，持续几天到她问你为什么这样做的时候，你就狠狠地对她说，“我嫌你烦！“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;只是，在我的姐姐身上，这法子一点效果都没有，反而感觉她还蛮幸福的，说我很懂事。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天发生的就又证明了这一点，本来姐姐心情蛮好的，自己开车去了超市，只是她回来以后放完东西，就开始心情很不好了，而且找了一个借口说不想动。只是我感觉她并没有那么不想动，她花力气把我赶走消耗的精神比陪我做蛋糕消耗的精神要大很多&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你想想把我锁在一个房间里得消耗多少力量。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;只是，妈妈也说了，她心情只是不稳定而已，等她心情好的时候，她人还是蛮好的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.29  妈妈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;上画画课的时候姐姐一直在看着我，不知道为什么她特别喜欢烦我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;正好需要画手，我让姐姐帮我画。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐认真的看着那个手，然后转过头来看着我说，“我真的不会画手的，你画的很好的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;也不知道姐姐为什么这么会装傻，平常一点都不会演戏的人竟然怎么会装傻。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我硬抓姐姐的手，她勉强的给我画了一个手，然后很有兴致地加了好几块肉。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;画完手后，姐姐觉得没事干了就不停的玩我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;只是我明明生下来不是给她玩的，像妈妈一直说的那样，生男孩子是拿来用的，生女孩子是拿来爱的，给姐姐生个妹妹，是给她爱的，给她当一辈子的最好的朋友，当闺蜜的。她好好应该听妈妈的话，好好爱我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈本来是个蛮好的妈妈。她现在在学佛，一直重复的对我说所有人的心里面都住了一个菩萨，只是因为被人的欲望给埋起来了，所以得把这些欲望给卸掉，用清静心供养心里的那个不爱理我的菩萨。我本来想象学佛的人肯定更善良，脾气也会好很多。只是这个人不光脾气没好很多，反而时常说自己心很静，一个人拍一下手，就会被吓一跳。然后被吓一跳的结果就是她的脾气会不好，会马上赶人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看到这里，你肯定会问，世界上会有谁怎么这么讲究的呢？那个人其实是我的妈妈。前几天她很骄傲的说，“我最近打坐又有长进，我现在一坐下来就能很静”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但本来她能正常的欢欢喜喜的跟我一起看电视。现在却说她只能忍耐地陪我看电视。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;大概因为有点内疚，我听到她问刘医生，“刘医生，现在我每次陪暖暖看电视，连看平常娱乐节目我都觉的好吵，更别说武侠剧了，这是什么原因呢？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;刘医生说，“很好哦，这说明你心更静了，是件好事”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“这样啊，”妈妈很开心只是看了看我，继续问刘医生，“可有没有方法减少一下看电视时或者生活中怕烦的情绪“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“这是个阶段，会过去的”刘医生的回答让妈妈很安心&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;因为刘医生的每句话都会让妈妈很安心&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;想到妈妈学佛，我还很担心她会像老子写的道德经里面说的把每个人都当刍狗。那她对我的感受就跟马路边的一个醉汉子一样了。而且学佛之后她对所有的东西都没要求了，就不能体会到我无限制的唠叨有多烦人了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;总而言之，学佛是件很难的事情，稍微把身体练练好就行了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.8  我的期待&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天饭桌上妈妈猛夸我和姐姐竟然会看着YOUTUBE发面团切面做出了面条，还相当好吃，我和姐姐听了都相当地得意，尤其这个面是我用脚踩出来的。唯有爸爸说，“你们下次应该试着做拉面，更有挑战性一点“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐说，”我看过做拉面的视频，做拉面其实蛮难的，而且会弄得很不干净“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸说，“一点都不难的，今天晚上我就拉个面给你看&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我很好奇，“你会拉面？你拉过面吗”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“我曾经在餐厅里面，看到过人拉面“爸爸回答&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“那我也看到过”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”而且我还这么聪明，最多再看一个视频就会了“爸爸听了我的话补充了一句，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我一直盯着爸爸，等他说完后说：”我会从嘴里喷火“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“喷火？你不能瞎讲的呀”爸爸依然在兴头上&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“没有瞎讲，因为我在马戏团表演看过喷火”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈听着又大笑，夸我聪明，反应快，表达精准&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸却还在他的世界里信口开河“你不能把这两样东西一起比的，喷火是有危险的，但做拉面。。。。。。“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“暖暖这是用夸张来表达”连姐姐也听出来了。姐姐早就吃完了，等不及了，开始把爸爸旁边的剩下一点点的菜抢了过去.因为现在收拾饭桌和洗碗是她的事，她想快点做完&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“喂，我还没吃好呢“爸爸一边叫， 一边快速的再抓了几口菜&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;而他讲要做拉面的事，很快忘了。。。。。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我曾经很期待，爸爸的成功的拉面。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>anneofthegreengables</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/anneofthegreengables/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 10:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/anneofthegreengables/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;anne of the green gables&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew and Marilla Cuthbert are siblings who live in Green Gables, Prince Edward Island. To help Matthew, who is getting too old to do the farm work on his own, they plan to adopt an orphan boy. At the train station, instead of a boy to do the farm work, the orphanage sent Anne Shirley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the ride back home, Matthew found that Anne’s wild imagination and talkativeness enjoys him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Marilla tucked Anne to bed, she told her to tell her prayers, and since she was not familiar she said an awfully ridiculous prayer. That was not it for her ridiculous actions, she wore a fancy flower wreath to church and more childish cute events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite multiple complaints from Marilla about Anne, Anne managed to stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne tried to behave as Marilla wanted, she was a cheerful and enthusiastic girl with plenty of imagination, but she lacks social manners and exquisite skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne never had friends back in the orphanage, she had to bear with her imaginative friends. She longed for friends for a long time, and thankfully she met Diana., her bosom friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anna was extremely exuberant for a new friend. Although she was bothered by the thought of Diana’s mother not approving of her poor “Lady manners”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One day, Anne invited Diana to a little tea party, instead of giving Diana her typical raspberry cordial., she gave Diana wine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, when Diana’s mother found out that Diana was drunk, she thought that Anne did it on purpose and forbidden Diana from hanging out with Anne.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Anne went to school , she met a boy named Gilbart. Anne despised him from the start since he made fun of her “carrot” hair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was excellent at her studies, as she devoted quite a lot in them. With her devotement, she manages to get a scholarship and attend four years of college for free which was quite her dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To share her accomplishment, Anne hurried back to Green Gables, where she heard that Matthew died out of a heart attack and Marilla is likely to go blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She acknowledges that Marilla needs someone to take care of herself. She decides to give up her chance to go to college and stayed at green gables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hearing the news, Gilbart gave up his work of being a teacher at a school near green gables as Anne would be closer to Marilla.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anne’s rivary with Gilbart has ceased, she understands where to put her devoteness but still was optimistic as before.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DoFacebookandotherformsofsocialmediaisolatepeoplefromeachother?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/dofacebookandotherformsofsocialmediaisolatepeoplefromeachother/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 06:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/dofacebookandotherformsofsocialmediaisolatepeoplefromeachother/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do Facebook and other forms of social media isolate people from each other?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that Social Media is used to maintain already existing relationships and more opportunities to meet new people. Social media is like a classroom but different types of people from different parts of the world are all gathered together. It has already replaced people’s old ways of communicating for example; letters, telephones, etc. About only 20 years ago, you had to pay to communicate with people, but now we can just easily communicate via social media. Now we can accomplish many things online; shopping, education, bonding relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m pretty shy in real life,  I just happen to be more outgoing online? My friend once said that I’m different online. She even wrote in my birthday card that I never filter my weird jokes. I made a lot more friends online than I did in real life. Back in second grade or something, I remember people giving me the “Talented Kid” Title and ignoring me. Saying it&amp;rsquo;s not safe for me to play this game since I&amp;rsquo;m “small”. (what is it like online? How is it different?)I think it&amp;rsquo;s easier to make friends online due to being more “Social” and you can configure yourself to be the “Better self”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the internet, you can lose nothing (Except for your reputation online of course), it allows people to express their own opinion more, and meet more people that support your opinion. Nothing will happen even if you offend someone. Of course, this makes social media more toxic. As human beings yearn for support and belonging. But social media is overall ok for me? Since I&amp;rsquo;m in a game/art community, just make sure you stay in a positive community if you&amp;rsquo;re on social media. I think social media makes people more open to others too. Even a few studies have linked that social support leads to positive mental health. ((&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.helpguide.org/articles/mental-health/social-media-and-mental-health.htm&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Studies info:&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Social Media has a lot of good things there is stuff quite disturbing and toxic on there. Lots of people are controversial and start arguments for no reason, the accounts with big followings always get the advantage. You either need to be a prodigy at something or do a lot of giveaways to get a large following count. And I find the accounts with big followings tend to isolate from their previous “Friends” after they grow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And a lot of people are very toxic, if you&amp;rsquo;re a big account, you get canceled if you post a little thing wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore, Social Media is easy to cause conflicts against people/your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social media also causes people to be less interactive IRL, you often set yourself higher online than in real life. And that could disappoint people if they ever meet you in real life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But those cases are very rare as you just have to stick in the positive communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore I believe that Social Media does not isolate people from each other but an opportunity to make new friends and bond your relationships with current ones.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Siddhartha悉达多</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/siddhartha%E6%82%89%E8%BE%BE%E5%A4%9A/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 07:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/siddhartha%E6%82%89%E8%BE%BE%E5%A4%9A/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Siddhartha wadcs the son of a Brahmin, his father was rich and respected. Siddhartha brought joy to people around him. However, Siddhartha wanted to seek enlightenment, something more than what his family provided for them. He tried ways his religion provided to him but it didn’t work out despite his efforts, he still was longing for something more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As he saw that his elderlys did not seek enlightenment, he decided to try a new path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few days, as he gazed out, he saw a group of Samanas begging for food, they had barely clothes.He was interested in their culture as it was quite different from his current way of living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He begged his father to join the Samanas, his father beauty refused but he was very persistent. His father knew that he could not stop him so he let Siddhartha join the Samanas. He soon learned to let go of his desires, the desires for love, money, everything providing him from entering his peaceful mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a while adapting to the Samanas culture, he realized it was not what he wanted, even the teachers and the elderly Samanas have yet to achieve the enlightenment Siddhartha was longing for. Therefor Govinda led Siddhartha to the buddha. Where the Buddha lived, everyone looked up to him. Govinda was eager to hear more about this holy person people talk upon. After a lesson from the Buddha, Govinda was convinced and eager to become an apprentice of his. But Siddhartha thought that the Buddha wont give him answers he longed for. As he said, the buddha has robbed him, he has robbed him out of his precious friend, but he had gave him more in return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Siddhartha was sad that Govinda had to leave him, he once thought that Govinda won&amp;rsquo;t walk a step without him, now that he decided on his own route. Siddhartha was truly happy for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Siddhartha wandered around for a long time, and here he found a small town.&lt;br&gt;
Siddhartha knew this charming girl named “Kamala”, he just knew that she was perfect for learning about love. But Kamala wanted a man with pockets full of money, Siddhartha only had ripped clothes back then. Kamala convinced him to be a merchant. With Kamala’s help, he soon was employed by a merchant, “Kamaswami” and began learning about the business world. Kamala became his lover and taught him about love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon, a few years passed, he became a successful merchant and had pockets full of money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He still thought that he longed for something more. One night, he decided to abandon everything here since he still thought he didn&amp;rsquo;t get what he longed for, instead he considered himself moving farther away from the “Enlightenment” He longed for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wandered around like a drunk man and he soon fell upon a river, he wanted to drown himself but he fell asleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Siddhartha was sleeping on the riverbank. Govinda (Now as a monk) saw a man sleeping beside a river, and was concerned, he didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize Siddhartha at all. But sat beside him protecting him from snakes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Govinda didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize Siddhartha, when Siddhartha woke up, he immediately recognized Govinda. Govinda said that Siddhartha changed quite significantly, he had now the look and attitude as a rich man, nothing compared to the man with no clothes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Govinda was now a monk, still a apprentice from the Buddha and did not yet seek enlightenment&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Siddhartha reached enlightenment at the end with the lessons of the riverman, he finally reached what he wanted for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favorite character is Kamala since shes cute and earnest and the others are just stupid. I think that Siddhartha was selfish by just leaving Kamala behind and only cares about his own “Enlightenment”. And Gamala doesn’t even know what he’s doing, he first followed Siddhartha since he thought he “Had a clue on what he‘s doing” and then he followed the Buddaha, its like he just follows the nearest person to him that he thinks has a idea on what they are doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My least favorite character is Buddaha, since he knows what he&amp;rsquo;s doing, he knows it&amp;rsquo;s wrong but he has a huge crowd of people surrounding him. And he dares not to tell them that they&amp;rsquo;ll never reach enlightenment with his help. Unlike the river guy, the Buddaha is not “Comfortable” In his “Enlightenment”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think that Siddhartha used a rather selfish way to reach his own enlightenment, he first left his father, then he ditched Govinda, and after that, he abandoned Kamala. He only really just caused trouble wherever he went. My sister told me that Herman wrote several books about people reaching enlightenment in their own paths. And Siddhartha went the slightly selfish path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was moved by Vasudeva’s speeches,he foreshadowed the timelessness of the river. Siddhartha soon realized that his life is also like a river. He brought Siddhartha back to Nirvinia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>TheSevenHabitsOfHighlyEffectiveTeens</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/thesevenhabitsofhighlyeffectiveteens/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 01:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/thesevenhabitsofhighlyeffectiveteens/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;|  You might wonder why this habit is the first one stated in the book. As the book explained, it&amp;rsquo;s because it&amp;rsquo;s the key to unlock all the other habits.  Proactive means that you could accept criticism and won&amp;rsquo;t fuss over something that is your fault. They don’t let their personal feelings take over themselves. If you could manage to be Proactive, it&amp;rsquo;ll help you be more responsible over your life. And even more happy! Since you&amp;rsquo;re not always pushing your emotions away to someone else. &lt;br&gt;
People are quite indecisive creatures. The stereotypical girls people speak of spend hours of time choosing a dress. Many people didn’t achieve that they exactly “want” in life because they didn&amp;rsquo;t have a goal in mind. You might ask, “Many people do that, they are simply attempting everything before choosing a specific goal, you shouldn’t set a time limit on choosing important stuff”. That is true but the longer you take, the easier it is for you to get farther away from what you truly want as a goal. By what? Well there are quite a few things, such as, other people’s opinions, jealousy, and too much consideration.  That&amp;rsquo;s why you should set a clear goal for yourself before you start on anything.&lt;br&gt;
This helps with managing your time/being more efficient. Putting what matters more first and what matters least last. This helps overcoming the difficult times with better time management. With time management, you won&amp;rsquo;t have to deal with rushing things at the last moment. This helps achieving your goal more efficiently with your prioritizing skills.&lt;br&gt;
Life is like a competition. In school, the students battle to get into better schools. After school, people battle to get better jobs. When they are old, they still have competitions going on in their head. It&amp;rsquo;s because humans are just very biased creatures. They want themselves to win everything. Because of that, we try to fix our mind for a more inclusive way of being biased.  Win-Win is a balance of being biased and inclusive. Therefore a positive way of thinking of things.&lt;br&gt;
A lot of teens aren&amp;rsquo;t patient. During the last five minutes of class, you can constantly see people looking at the clock. But during teamwork, if the same batch of teens aren’t understood, they get impatient and frustrated. This habit is an important communication skill. &lt;br&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure yall all heard of “Your way, My way, Or the highway”. Basically meaning they have to listen to you or they leave. But it shouldn’t be archived like that, if you fix it up; “Your way, My way, Or a Higher way” .That does sound a lot better doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? Everyone should negotiate while teamwork. Appreciating others&amp;rsquo; hard work.&lt;br&gt;
Everyone should try to be the “Better themselves”, constantly improving and improvising. Constantly  Improvising the “four key dimensions by life” the body, heart, brain, and soul |  &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/a-/AOh14Giag0e-oISIXZFNOQ9J1G1x0_-qkWexEVTtp1e_Vw=s80&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/a-/AOh14Giag0e-oISIXZFNOQ9J1G1x0_-qkWexEVTtp1e_Vw=s80&lt;/a&gt; |  回复转发&lt;br&gt;
&amp;mdash;|&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/u/0/settings/storage?hl=zh-CN&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_source=gmail&amp;amp;utm_campaign=manage_storage&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.google.com/intl/zh-CN/policies/terms/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.google.com/intl/zh-CN/policies/privacy/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.google.com/gmail/about/policy/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Introduction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be Proactive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You might wonder why this habit is the first one stated in the book. As the book explained, it&amp;rsquo;s because it&amp;rsquo;s the key to unlock all the other habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Proactive means that you could accept criticism and won&amp;rsquo;t fuss over something that is your fault. They don’t let their personal feelings take over themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you could manage to be Proactive, it&amp;rsquo;ll help you be more responsible over your life. And even more happy! Since you&amp;rsquo;re not always pushing your emotions away to someone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin With the End in Mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People are quite indecisive creatures. The stereotypical girls people speak of spend hours of time choosing a dress. Many people didn’t achieve that they exactly “want” in life because they didn&amp;rsquo;t have a goal in mind. You might ask, “Many people do that, they are simply attempting everything before choosing a specific goal, you shouldn’t set a time limit on choosing important stuff”. That is true but the longer you take, the easier it is for you to get farther away from what you truly want as a goal. By what? Well there are quite a few things, such as, other people’s opinions, jealousy, and too much consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s why you should set a clear goal for yourself before you start on anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Put First Things First&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This helps with managing your time/being more efficient. Putting what matters more first and what matters least last. This helps overcoming the difficult times with better time management. With time management, you won&amp;rsquo;t have to deal with rushing things at the last moment. This helps achieve your goal more efficiently with your prioritizing skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Think Win-Win&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life is like a competition. In school, the students battle to get into better schools. After school, people battle to get better jobs. When they are old, they still have competitions going on in their head. It&amp;rsquo;s because humans are just very biased creatures. They want themselves to win everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of that, we try to fix our mind for a more inclusive way of being biased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Win-Win is a balance of being biased and inclusive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Therefore a positive way of thinking of things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Seek First to Understand, Then to Be Understood&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of teens aren&amp;rsquo;t patient. During the last five minutes of class, you can constantly see people looking at the clock. But during teamwork, if the same batch of teens aren’t understood, they get impatient and frustrated. This habit is an important communication skill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synergize&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure you all heard of “Your way, My way, Or the highway”. Basically meaning they have to listen to you or they leave. But it shouldn’t be archived like that, if you fix it up; “Your way, My way, Or a Higher way” .That does sound a lot better doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? Everyone should negotiate while teamwork. Appreciating others&amp;rsquo; hard work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;7&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharpen the Saw&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone should try to be the “Better themselves”, constantly improving and improvising. Constantly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Improvising the “four key dimensions by life” the body, heart, brain, and soul&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2020中文暑假日记</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 09:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;638&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_0_hue8676028dce69cf1e96e74bd029c356f_289268_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_0_hue8676028dce69cf1e96e74bd029c356f_289268_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;110px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;838&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_1_huc4c27c7162d8f99d580fd02bfb93e940_1345795_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_1_huc4c27c7162d8f99d580fd02bfb93e940_1345795_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;60&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;145px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;790&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_2_hu222912336a4fc7784fd1b1bd8e64a244_590054_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_2_hu222912336a4fc7784fd1b1bd8e64a244_590054_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;57&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;137px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;638&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_3_hu6bce258561e6f16cb7d253215650fce0_215591_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%9A%91%E5%81%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/image_3_hu6bce258561e6f16cb7d253215650fce0_215591_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;110px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.29  妈妈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;上画画课的时候姐姐一直在看着我，不知道为什么她特别喜欢烦我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;正好需要画手，我让姐姐帮我画。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐认真的看着那个手，然后转过头来看着我说，“我真的不会画手的，你画的很好的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;也不知道姐姐为什么这么会装傻，平常一点都不会演戏的人竟然怎么会装傻。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我硬抓姐姐的手，她勉强的给我画了一个手，然后很有兴致地加了好几块肉。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;画完手后，姐姐觉得没事干了就不停的玩我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;只是我明明生下来不是给她玩的，像妈妈一直说的那样，生男孩子是拿来用的，生女孩子是拿来爱的，给姐姐生个妹妹，是给她爱的，给她当一辈子的最好的朋友，当闺蜜的。她好好应该听妈妈的话，好好爱我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈本来是个蛮好的妈妈。她现在在学佛，一直重复的对我说所有人的心里面都住了一个菩萨，只是因为被人的欲望给埋起来了，所以得把这些欲望给卸掉，用清静心供养心里的那个不爱理我的菩萨。我本来想象学佛的人肯定更善良，脾气也会好很多。只是这个人不光脾气没好很多，反而时常说自己心很静，一个人拍一下手，就会被吓一跳。然后被吓一跳的结果就是她的脾气会不好，会马上赶人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看到这里，你肯定会问，世界上会有谁怎么这么讲究的呢？那个人其实是我的妈妈。前几天她很骄傲的说，“我最近打坐又有长进，我现在一坐下来就能很静”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但本来她能正常的欢欢喜喜的跟我一起看电视。现在却说她只能忍耐地陪我看电视。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;大概因为有点内疚，我听到她问刘医生，“刘医生，现在我每次陪暖暖看电视，连看平常娱乐节目我都觉的好吵，更别说武侠剧了，这是什么原因呢？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;刘医生说，“很好哦，这说明你心更静了，是件好事”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“这样啊，”妈妈很开心只是看了看我，继续问刘医生，“可有没有方法减少一下看电视时或者生活中怕烦的情绪“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“这是个阶段，会过去的”刘医生的回答让妈妈很安心&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;因为刘医生的每句话都会让妈妈很安心&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;想到妈妈学佛，我还很担心她会像老子写的道德经里面说的把每个人都当刍狗。那她对我的感受就跟马路边的一个醉汉子一样了。而且学佛之后她对所有的东西都没要求了，就不能体会到我无限制的唠叨有多烦人了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;总而言之，学佛是件很难的事情，稍微把身体练练好就行了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.8  我的期待&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天饭桌上妈妈猛夸我和姐姐竟然会看着YOUTUBE发面团切面做出了面条，还相当好吃，我和姐姐听了都相当地得意，尤其这个面是我用脚踩出来的。唯有爸爸说，“你们下次应该试着做拉面，更有挑战性一点“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐说，”我看过做拉面的视频，做拉面其实蛮难的，而且会弄得很不干净“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸说，“一点都不难的，今天晚上我就拉个面给你看&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我很好奇，“你会拉面？你拉过面吗”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“我曾经在餐厅里面，看到过人拉面“爸爸回答&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“那我也看到过”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”而且我还这么聪明，最多再看一个视频就会了“爸爸听了我的话补充了一句，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我一直盯着爸爸，等他说完后说：”我会从嘴里喷火“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“喷火？你不能瞎讲的呀”爸爸依然在兴头上&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“没有瞎讲，因为我在马戏团表演看过喷火”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈听着又大笑，夸我聪明，反应快，表达精准&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸却还在他的世界里信口开河“你不能把这两样东西一起比的，喷火是有危险的，但做拉面。。。。。。“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“暖暖这是用夸张来表达”连姐姐也听出来了。姐姐早就吃完了，等不及了，开始把爸爸旁边的剩下一点点的菜抢了过去.因为现在收拾饭桌和洗碗是她的事，她想快点做完&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“喂，我还没吃好呢“爸爸一边叫， 一边快速的再抓了几口菜&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;而他讲要做拉面的事，很快忘了。。。。。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我曾经很期待，爸爸的成功的拉面。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.21&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我的爸爸：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐一到餐桌, 看到本来她盛的两碗饭一碗变多了，一碗变少了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她马上转身看了一下爸爸，心里已经大概明白答案了，可是还是问了一声，“爸爸，怎么一碗饭多了，一碗少了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸很骄傲的说，“暖暖在长身体,得多吃一点“ ，后面还跟着补了一句, “你看，我多伟大，牺牲了自己就为了让你们吃多一点“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是，我其实是吃不下那么多的.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我非常勉强的忍受了他的善意, 他真的是宽容心太大了，一样都不少. 加完饭以后还加菜，一边说着，“你过两年想长也不能长了，男孩最多能长到十八岁, 可是女孩子只能长到13岁, 好好珍惜这两年.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我听说很多小孩子小时候一直背唐诗，我相信爸爸小时候就一直在背大道理。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;客厅外，突然听见一声大叫，“暖暖，吃完饭我要看你的数学的！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这时，我立马开始行动,。只听见房间外一大堆噼里啪啦的门和抽屉被翻来翻去。终算找到一个合格的地方。把纸塞到一个袋子下面。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;吃完饭后，他竟然不管。直到我发作业的时候，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我看他还不问就把我的数学拿出来了，他拿了一个杯子路过说，“你是我的女儿，数学对你来说应该是简单到不算是一个事“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我马上忽视了他这些非常自恋的观点。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;因为我和姐姐都习惯了爸爸一直在显摆自己从小怎么全班最高分，虽然他明明也承认了自己小学的时候很落后的。只是他竟然能把小学的时候的落后最后发扬成正能量的优点。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天，爸爸一直在抱怨我们怎么会在吃饭的时候做蛋糕&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后我不知道回应了些什么，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸说，“你就像妈妈，你跟她都一样坏“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我说，“女儿都是遗传爸爸的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;他愣住了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈大笑，直夸我聪明反应快&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其实爸爸一般都会说我和姐姐每个好的地方都遗传他，不好的地方都是遗传妈妈，特别是遗传了妈妈的坏。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>中文日记：妈妈的生日&#43;母亲节</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 11:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;700&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/image_0_hu34f04d118fd93667c4b11264ab9985d2_629810_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/image_0_hu34f04d118fd93667c4b11264ab9985d2_629810_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;50&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;121px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;638&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/image_1_hu4abfb7dbe70f12d870a2847acd95c18a_663226_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%A6%88%E5%A6%88%E7%9A%84%E7%94%9F%E6%97%A5-%E6%AF%8D%E4%BA%B2%E8%8A%82/image_1_hu4abfb7dbe70f12d870a2847acd95c18a_663226_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;110px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.16&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;母亲节之前，妈妈说她很想要礼物的。姐姐给他画了一张卡，只画了我坐在一个很大的兔子上面，可是想了一下，这其实不是妈妈喜欢的而是我喜欢的。所以就擦掉了.  大概想要我帮忙，所以就跑下来，问我可不可以画妈妈。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我说，“你知道我最最不喜欢画人的，可是我能做点纸花，然后再做个巧克力蛋糕”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说“啊，我做这些好了，你去画妈妈”。吵来吵去后，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸来了，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我跟爸爸说，“你让姐姐干自己擅长的事”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐说：“你让暖暖多点信心”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后爸爸被我们搞晕了就走了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐说，“我们也做不了吃的，所以我们点很多外卖把！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**&lt;br&gt;
**&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最后就买了一大堆食物包括凉皮，还有做了很多很多荷包蛋。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;姐姐还画了一个小女孩吊在气球上的卡。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;就这样，母亲节我们一家开开心心地就吃了一天的好吃的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说，她吃了七个荷包蛋。生日不想再吃同样的了。叫我们开动脑筋，继续努力，拿出爱心，再接再励！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>中文日记：疫情里和姐姐的每一天</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 07:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;646&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/image_0_hub978b97b42cf184026208852829a986a_334865_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/image_0_hub978b97b42cf184026208852829a986a_334865_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;112px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;638&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/image_1_hucbbdf057472b498fdd4b6d28ae643294_288240_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E7%96%AB%E6%83%85%E9%87%8C%E5%92%8C%E5%A7%90%E5%A7%90%E7%9A%84%E6%AF%8F%E4%B8%80%E5%A4%A9/image_1_hucbbdf057472b498fdd4b6d28ae643294_288240_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;46&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;110px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2020中文日记</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 07:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2020%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;5.5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近有一个传染病毒，因为蛮严重的。所以现在没有人敢出去了，都在家里的被单里面躺着。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是虽然呆在家里，可是老是觉得没安全感，所以就把家里用的东西都买回来了，还多买了十倍。这至少我还能理解,可是实在不明白为什么很多人买了很多家都平常都不用的东西。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;就比方说是巧克力，卫生纸之类。病毒之前，他们还觉得巧克力糖分这么高的东西，谁还会吃这种垃圾食品。可是现在，连做蛋糕的大块大块的很苦的巧克力都没了。难道人人都在家里吃巧克力么？也不可能啊！大概他们觉得，买了很多乱七八糟的东西就有安全感，也不知道为什么。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我写了这么多，看的人应该都明白，巧克力没了对我。。。。，最近找到一个微波炉的巧克力蛋糕的配方可是现在也不能做了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我最喜欢的饮料一直是珍珠奶茶，里面有奶香和茶香。可是有没有单独喝茶的那种苦味。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;最近，正好家里找了一个奶茶的配分。简单的说，就是泡一杯浓到差不多是黑色的红茶，为了让奶茶变淡一点，再倒一罐淡奶.做完上面这些步骤，就好了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;淡奶虽然在可丽饼上面看上去很好吃，可是其实很粘的。姐姐的头发碰到了一点就臭掉了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;只是那天我们是晚上做的。好多人都说，不能在晚上喝奶茶因为里面有太  多咖啡因。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天做了满满的一锅。虽然家里没有珍珠，我就用奶油代替了。虽然他们的口味是完全不同的，可是两个都是我喜欢的，所以也无所谓的.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈总说，珍珠奶茶的珍珠是塑料做的。可是他们其实是用面粉做的。可是妈妈还是坚持说他们是塑料做的。难道有人会把塑料磨成粉的？我也不太懂。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;总之，珍珠奶茶是个很好吃的饮料，只是所有人都低估他了而已。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.9&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这半年因为有corona virus疫情，所以导致没人敢出门，据说超市都被人翻空了，连点个外卖。都得用消毒水喷一遍。街上少了很多人。学校也不上课了。我们一家四口每天都得待在家里，每个人都蹲在家里什么事情也不能干，只能打打游戏，做做作业。不过呢，呆在家里还是蛮好玩的，就这样想，在家里躺在床上总比坐在一个学校的椅子上做作业好。虽然家里面很无聊，至少家里能做一点饼干，烤点串吃。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天吃完午饭，太阳照在草地上，清凉的风渐渐的扫过花园。我跟Ayma约了一次通话。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“滴滴！”终于盼来了电话铃，我们开始很开心地聊天，我问了问她隔离好不好玩，并且跟她推荐了几个我喜欢的漫画。她给我看了一下她的电脑上面的一个学习网站Showbie。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我问“你看这个干嘛”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她问，“你学校作业做完了么？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“学校都没开始呢‘，我说&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“”啊！学校其实早在Showbie上有作业了“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”你完成了么？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”当然！早就完成了，你呢？”电话声音里听得出她的骄傲&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这一次我不作声了,假装没有听见她的话似的&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‘你没做完吗？！“她吃惊的叫了一声&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这时，已经入睡的妈妈，在沙发上迷迷糊糊喊了一声，“你们能不能小声一点”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;于是，我放低声音说”根本没有作业！你搞错了“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”你去看看老师最新给你发的邮件“ 她继续，“要么发给你爸爸了，要么发给你妈妈了。你仔细去查查“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;于是，我到妈妈的电脑上认真的看了一看所有学校老师发来的信，没有一点点要马上上课的意思。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她并不介意问到，“那你showbie上有作业么？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”没“ 我痛快的答道&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”那你邮件里面有没有一封信，让你交作业？“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”没” 但这次我声音里面有一点怀疑&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“肯定有的！我好像上上个星期五已经交了。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“这不可能！”我实在忍不住了，也不等Ayma问我了，喊起来“根本没有作业！老师是想要你上的是TEAMS。一点没布置过作业。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这时候，Ayma已经准备把电话挂了，我看到他爸爸给她了一个热狗。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;去年，老师为了培养我们的leadership，让我们班是照顾05班的小孩子，也就是幼儿园的孩子，也就是那些整天规定穿着黄色的背心的孩子们。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我们得在他们休息的时间看着他们。其实呢，他们把自己照顾的好好的，实在有事情的时候，他们会跑过来找我们的，可是老师还是不放心。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;他们每天recess前都得把满满的一罐水果都吃光。我看着真的有点可怜他们，我小时候可没有这种奇怪的规则。在我看来，他们还有一个不必要的规则。上课的铃响了以后，得排列起来，每个头都数一遍。可是没一个小孩听你话的，都在四处乱跑，排的队也是弯弯曲曲的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;于是，老师换了一个规则，让他们先跑到教室，再数。平时我都是先到了，找了一个靠后的位置站着。跟着一个一个孩子到了，害的我一个一个位置都让给他们，排到了最后面。老师还在不停的数。老师数了一遍又数了一遍，我一直在想为什么。当老师数到我的时候，念了一声“哎？怎么多了一个？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我说：“我是个student leader。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;老师恍然大悟，尴尬的说“ 啊，你长的。。。很可爱！嗯，长得非常可爱！“。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“谢谢”，我小声回了句，边想这全怪我也穿的黄色背心，边赶去上音乐课了。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2020.3RTwriting1</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2020.3rtwriting1/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 12:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2020.3rtwriting1/</guid>
        <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a peaceful little wood in the depths of a boisterous city. The woods weren’t like the city at all. It was a lovely wood with evergreen trees all over and a pond which shimmered when the sun illuminated the water. Fishes joyfully splashing water and paradise birds chirping joyfully in those branches. Wind passes by causing willows to blow elegantly. And in the middle of this wood, there was a little red cabin. Even though it’s petite, it&amp;rsquo;s quite dainty. Th,,e windows were elegantly covered without even a dash of dust. The door was made out of wood, with some panels carved with caution. The chimney always had freshly made bread rising out of it. In that dainty little cabin, lived a joyful family, two boys and a mother and a father. Quite a normal family to be honest. The elder brother, Noah, was almost an adult. And the younger brother, Liam, was only a teenager. The start was fine, it was just like a normal family though a bit lonely because the father was often on trips due to the little amount of jobs in the woods. And the mother was busy due to the household. Liam was always quite lonely and life was quite dull. But Noah was always there to accompany him and support him, not minding the age gap. But when time passed, Noah grew into an adult, and he soon left the little cabin to develop his own little family in the city due to better circumstances and passion for getting a well-paid job. But Liam was heartbroken when his elder brother left. He soon became all gloomy, his family didn’t know what to do. They gave him a better room, made him go to school, but it didn’t seem to get better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until one day, while his father was hunting for food since it was hunting season. He found a little pup wandering in the woods. It didn’t seem like it was from the woods, more like it wandered away from the city due to it being a little pug, and it had a glimmering little collar even though it was covered with dust and ashes. It looked helplessly at the father, and the father couldn’t stand the guilt of not bringing a little lost pup to a welcoming home. So the father flipped through his messy backpack, finally finding a rough braided string, and used it as a leash to bring the dog home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dog ran around, sniffing everything it saw. It wasn’t quite obedient either, for it lived in the wild. It attacked everything that wiggled. In his perspective, everything was a deadly beast, probably due to the terrifying wildness in the woods, even though it was an elegant little wood. There was a part far away from it, it was quite the contrary to this wood. It was full of withered trees, blood traces leaked from the pond. Miserable shrieks echoed down the woods, every little animal at the bottom of the animal cycle was erased. And it was even more terrifying since it was hunting season. The stars were almost covered by the trees, multiple flashing eyes seem to be coming out of the trees. Guns reloading and shooting, stampede hooves pounding on the ground. It was a miracle that this little pug pup was still alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the cabin, it was terrified, yelping, cuddled up in a little corner. The parents tried to approach the scared pug, concluding with the pug slamming the door and hiding in the closet. Liam, at that time, was doodling behind the clothes in the closet. The pug was awfully afraid of Liam and tried to act aggressive. Liam giggled at the pug and the pug was no longer afraid. The pug became Liam’s best friend; he helped him overcome his fear, his shadows and his loneliness. And Liam helped the pug get over his shadows and aggressiveness. For them it was a win-win, but not for long. The pug rams his head into the couch cushions and launches his butt into the air, snuffling and growling excitedly.He achieves a partial headstand and his hind legs kick wildly. He is the embodiment of joy, and that joy is infectious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They played together every single day, the sun illuminating them. The trees were almost dancing and the animals seemed to be having fun. The world seemed to be smiling down at them. But as they say: “Time is a  river. Happy those who allow themselves to be carried, unresisting, with the current. They float through easy days. They live, unquestioning, in the moment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(I don’t want the dog to die anymore, it’s too tragic xD)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>中文：读后感-《射雕英雄传》</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 中文：读后感-《射雕英雄传》" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;870&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_0_hub39330c9f0de6500410a0eb8d1258722_1510040_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_0_hub39330c9f0de6500410a0eb8d1258722_1510040_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;920&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_1_hu234dfd087947cd7a914c48ab6b64e725_1270140_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_1_hu234dfd087947cd7a914c48ab6b64e725_1270140_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;150&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;360px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;778&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_2_huf86d8ed9b8890ed2ec68a2481eba1023_1373910_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_2_huf86d8ed9b8890ed2ec68a2481eba1023_1373910_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;56&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;135px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;834&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_3_hudad1a6c4b2a66e866005389bb13011dd_1272746_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_3_hudad1a6c4b2a66e866005389bb13011dd_1272746_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;60&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;145px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;782&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_4_huf4836eb75f2024742b1388c3ea4feafb_1466283_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_4_huf4836eb75f2024742b1388c3ea4feafb_1466283_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;56&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;136px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_5.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1056&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_5_hu02f9f994227b229559e932b007157343_1398517_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E8%AF%BB%E5%90%8E%E6%84%9F-%E5%B0%84%E9%9B%95%E8%8B%B1%E9%9B%84%E4%BC%A0/image_5_hu02f9f994227b229559e932b007157343_1398517_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;76&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;183px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Maybethat’sHermia’sfate.</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/maybethatshermiasfate./</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 08:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/maybethatshermiasfate./</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The tremendous trees gently sweeping the floor. From afar, it looks like millions of silk ribbons made out of an unremarkable shade of green. The fallen flower petals arise into the sky, causing a beautiful flower rain. The cheerful chirping flowers and the beautiful smell of flowers. There are more flowers than I could ever count, she swore she tried to count them. Those rainbow flowers fluttering in the sky was the last scene she recounted. “O! What shame it is to leave this place” She exclaimed before emptiness took over her. Her vision got blurrier and blurrier and blurrier, to the point she fainted. She did not recall anything after that. After a while, she woke up on a pile of twigs, at least that’s what she thought it was. Her eyes twitched a few time, and her eyes slowly opened. She deliberately got up from the “Pile of twigs”. “Am I in a barn? What is this rusty place?” She wondered. She felt like she forgot something, but she still remembers her home… When she arose, she realized it was much more than a “Pile of twigs” It was beautiful, but not quite as nice as the garden she recalls barely. The twigs were twisted together to make a dainty little garden bench. The ends had daisy rings thrown on it. All of it was made by terribly common materials, but it was so much more dainty than those stubborn chairs back in the village. She shivered while recalling the terrible memory. She sometimes wonders, if people could elaborate on everything they make with their either hands or mind. Wouldn’t the world be a lot better? She lowered her head and shook her head, her curled long hair was untied and the hair tie fell to the ground. But she was so deep into thought, didn’t even notice. She slowly rose her head and gently tucked her hair beside her ear, and spotted a shining river from about a stroll from where she was. And indeed, she went for a stroll to the river. “Where am I even? Why am I wandering around here? I should possibly find a way home&amp;hellip;” she thought on the way. Without realizing, she was already at her destination. Her reflection shined in the water, suddenly she remembered something. “H-Hermia” She whispered into her ear several times Hermia remembered everything, her village, her past life, the garden. Hermia looked into the river again, she observed herself. A girl with long curvy almond hair, ending around her knees, a dainty little face with freckles, eyes sparkling of curiosity, slightly pouty lips, ears slightly pointier than normal ears, a rustful circular black glasses. That’s who Hermia saw, she continued looking downwards. A slim neck, small shoulders, an elegant torso covered with a long white dress ending at her knees, long pianist hands, long slim legs that&amp;rsquo;s nearly skin and bones, and a little moon birthmark near her knees. Hermia suddenly heard a song, arousing her, she couldn’t help but follow the song. Days, days and days of walking. The song becoming louder, louder and louder. Her eyes were no longer bright and curious, her hair was no longer neat and curled, her cloth was no longer even white. But the “Birthmark” Got darker and darker. Until one day, the moon birthmark shined a tremendous white light. It wont stop glowing. Soon she became blind by the light, she cried all night and moaned in her sleep. She realized she was back in the garden, she recalled “The cheerful chirping flowers and the beautiful smell of flowers.” “The trees gently sweeping the floor” She busted into tears and embraced the flowers. Suddenly her body went light, lighter than a feather. Still embracing the flowers, she flew towards the sky. The roots of the flowers got tugged out and withered. Hermia held on to the flowers with all her might while she flied&amp;hellip;towards the sky. Hermia’s slept a day, two days, three days, until she couldn’t count. She was still soaring upwards. The flowers were all withered, except the one in the middle. Still bright as ever, still blooming, never ending. Maybe that’s Hermia’s fate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>G4:--Homework</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post G4:--Homework" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1036&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_0_hu411215db5932eeaabed5d6d38c911262_1293409_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_0_hu411215db5932eeaabed5d6d38c911262_1293409_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;75&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;180px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;978&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_1_hu6d1a6d241f40adad1314896d7cae31b5_1331599_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/g4--homework/image_1_hu6d1a6d241f40adad1314896d7cae31b5_1331599_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;141&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;338px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2018.2 暖暖日记（八岁三个月）</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 2018.2 暖暖日记（八岁三个月）" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.28&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;根据这个图，构思一个故事。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;注意表达结构的运用。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1、往往几个场景就把故事讲清楚了。不啰嗦。&lt;br&gt;
2、前面是平铺直叙，但有时候中间发生转折，还有的结尾出人意料。&lt;br&gt;
怎么让你的故事更加精彩呢？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;468&#34;
	height=&#34;298&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0_hu3921d977dc37eb0e83e64475c4160a2b_190839_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0_hu3921d977dc37eb0e83e64475c4160a2b_190839_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;157&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;376px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这是个关于蝴蝶，蜗牛和黄油面包的故事。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;有一天，蝴蝶在飞,突然有一只蜗牛出现了，蜗牛说，“你要跟我比赛么？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;蝴蝶说，“我懒的跟你比赛”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;蜗牛说，“如果你赢的话，我就给你一块黄油面包吃”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;蝴蝶马上就兴奋说，“好呀，好呀”因为蝴蝶的名字就叫BUTTERFLY，跟黄油面包BUTTERBREAD的感觉很像。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;为了防止跑步比赛的时候，万一下雨翅膀可以不湿的落下来，蝴蝶打算自己做把伞，所以马上回家做了一个很大很大的黄油三明治，打算下雨的时候躲在下面。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是不幸的是，蜗牛做了一个能变大的PIXIE DUST 。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比赛的那一天，蝴蝶骑在黄油面包上面飞去赛场，蜗牛把自己变得天一样大，才匆匆忙忙去赛场的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;巨大蜗牛还没吃饭就到赛场了，它看到了蝴蝶的黄油面包就完全馋了，一大口就吃掉了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比赛开始了，蝴蝶很担心，因为它的黄油面包雨伞被蜗牛吃掉了，跑了一半路真的下雨了，蝴蝶匆匆飞到蜗牛的壳里面去了。这样它们都有一个暖和的地方。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这样，它们同时到达终点，都赢了。于是，它们都请了对方吃黄油面包。但是蜗牛太小气了，加上它太懒了，蝴蝶请了蜗牛吃一大大块黄油面包，蜗牛只请回了蝴蝶一小块黄油面包。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE END&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.25 偷吃人参果，是谁的错 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;306&#34;
	height=&#34;204&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_1_hueb9685129c0cedd81be3fce95630b6b8_102205_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_1_hueb9685129c0cedd81be3fce95630b6b8_102205_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;150&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;360px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;《西游记》里偷吃人参果，大部分人都会认为是悟空的错，我今天写这个日记的原因就是想要证明在这个故事里没有一个人是完全对的或者完全错的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;首先，人参果没犯错，它们只是长得可爱了一点，才会惨被吃掉。人参果应该怪的是唐僧，因为如果唐僧把人参果吃下去的话，后面的悲剧就都不会发生了。清风和明月就不会把人参果吃掉。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是也不是完全是唐僧的错，清风和明月就非常贪吃，是她们先吃的，所以她们有一部分的错。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;八戒听见清风和明月在吃人参果，八戒就馋了，“馋”就是八戒名字里面一个得戒掉的一样事情，所以八戒也有一部分的错。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后呢，八戒被清风踢飞了，踢到了悟空那里，八戒本来就不应该把这事情告诉悟空，因为全世界都知道悟空最最热爱的就是桃子和长生不老。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其实呢这个故事的本质就是呢，是镇元大仙的错，因为呢，他没把人参果公平地分配，如果他给的是公平的数量，每个人就会各各满足，一起开开心心的吃人参果，就不会有这个故事了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是也不能说就是这个神仙的错，这个故事里面没有一个人是完全对的或者完全错的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2018.2.20 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_2.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;303&#34;
	height=&#34;134&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_2_hucae3011b61e8a7b99e6d9d33652909f1_18463_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_2_hucae3011b61e8a7b99e6d9d33652909f1_18463_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;226&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;542px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我今天对爸爸用“调虎离山”计。因为今天是我的PLAYDAY，我想在拿我的I PAD，而IPAD在爸爸妈妈的房间里，为了好玩（爸爸很好玩的）我打算用“调虎离山”计。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;调虎离山计里面你得把“王”拿掉然后呢就好办了。房间里只有爸爸这么一个人，所以我只有把他引走就行了。我一进房间，爸爸就问我,“干什么？”我没说我是来拿I pad，说了就用不成计了。所以呢，我就跟他说，“你得下去吃晚饭了。”但他肯定知道我在有“调虎离山”计，因为他坚决地说，“我不去！！！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;过了几分钟真正要吃饭了，他还不下来，他说要打电话，为了不让妈妈老烦他下去吃晚饭，他让我去用围魏救赵，瞒天过海，声东击西，空城计。。。。。。反正意思就是让我去围住妈妈不要去烦他。但我没这样干，用了三十六计最后一计，走为上策， 我饿了，要去吃晚饭了。。。。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2018.2.18 过年 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_3.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;124&#34;
	height=&#34;62&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_3_huae0bb339cdfeca8ea55879ef0dc91b1d_4579_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_3_huae0bb339cdfeca8ea55879ef0dc91b1d_4579_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;200&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;480px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天是年初二，在加拿大过新年是一件最最无聊的事情,一点都不好玩。反而很普通。你看这篇日记前先要把中国的热闹忘掉。因为在这里正相反，无聊，非常普通。现在我就围绕着“无聊，普通”这个中心点讲一讲我新年是怎么过的：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;学校里新年头几天都没有一个PD day, 更过分连一个派对都没有，最最受不了就是学校只有一个游戏表演，可那个表演差级了！！学校新年零食也准备的很差，只是饼干！我看到的时候快要疯掉了，可想不到放在嘴里还是蛮好吃的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;除了学校以外,在家里也还有很多无聊的事情呢,比方天天早饭都吃年糕是一个非常好的例子，也算是最无聊的。到处拜年也是非常糟糕的一个活动，得拿一个电话，不停地对着它很傻的说“新年快乐！！”更烦的就是在家里依然需要天天做作业 瞧，我现在就在写日记，超级超级普通和无聊。我最最讨厌做作业！！！新年在家最最最无聊的事情就是需要吃很多的饭, 我爸妈和阿姨（特别是爸爸）总是在试着把我喂成猪，因为我怎么喂也喂不成猪。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ 新年都未有芳华，二月初惊见草芽。白雪却嫌春色晚，故穿庭树作飞花。”我们这里新年这几天也下了超级大的雪，本来这可以算作一件不普通的事，可是这就搞得春天比冬天更冷，所以千千万万不要在过新年的时候来加拿大。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;题目：早春&lt;br&gt;
根据苏轼的诗《惠崇春江晚景》--竹外桃花三两枝，春江水暖鸭先知。蒌蒿满地芦芽短，正是河豚欲上时。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;提炼背后的模式，写一篇小作文。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;要求：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1，这首诗是讲春天的变化。小作文的题目可以是“春天来了”。1，总的变化 2，视觉：3，触觉：感受到什么4，味觉：吃的东西怎么样了。5，总结&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2，根据这首诗的模式，可以提炼出这些感官的活动。 从这个角度去观察早春。从多种感官的角度。 所以观察不仅仅是看，还要动用多种感官，协同进行。 3，尽量运用，引用最近学的二十首唐诗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_4.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;239&#34;
	height=&#34;69&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_4_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_10007_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_4_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_10007_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;346&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;831px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天是立春的第二天，在后花园里，“竹外桃花三两枝”，蓝莓，玉兰开始有花苞了，这让我非常烦，早春真的是要来了。我感觉早春是一年里最最冷的时候，这两天外面吹大大的风，重点是我们学校规定休息的时候所有人都必须去操场，我想坐着安静的情绪总要被打扰。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“天街小雨润如酥，草色遥看近却无”的早春里，没完没了的下雨是非常无聊的事情，你只能坐在没有雨的地方看书，但旁边总会有一大堆人在唧唧呱呱，烦。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;早春来了，“正是河豚欲上时”，笋也跟着上市了，就是熊猫的最爱，因为熊猫只吃笋和竹子，熊猫一定比我更很开心早春的到来。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我希望我有能力能消灭早春，盼望“春光懒困倚微， 桃花一簇开无主，可爱深红爱浅红”的春天快点到来。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.5 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_5.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;89&#34;
	height=&#34;89&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_5_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_4707_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_5_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_4707_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爱兔说 （仿写爱莲说）&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;动物都是很卡通的。妈妈独爱鼠。自有狗以来，世人皆爱狗。予独爱兔。兔能帮我吃蔬菜，十分可爱，蹦蹦跳跳，毛毛绒绒，可抱玩焉而不可不理。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;予谓鼠，动物之最聪明也；狗，胆子大也；兔，可爱也。噫！鼠之爱，妈妈之最也，兔之爱，同予者何人?狗之爱，宜乎众矣。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.2  &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_6.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;109&#34;
	height=&#34;67&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_6_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_7112_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.2-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%89%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_6_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_7112_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;162&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;390px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天，妈妈在给我讲《史记》和坏皇帝的事，等我听到昏君和暴君不一样，昏君主要管吃喝玩乐的，我很羡慕！所以我今天的日记主题就是“暖暖要当昏君”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当一个昏君应该是个非常简单的事情，吃喝玩乐不是一件非常简单的事情吗？这么简单的事暖暖一定能做好！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;吃喝玩乐4样东西我都能做到！！不在话下！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;吃＝吃点心&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;喝＝喝珍珠奶茶+热巧克力&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;玩＝玩毛绒兔子&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;乐＝抱妈妈。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;瞧，我把吃喝玩乐的计划排的多么好。如果你的国家需要一个坏皇帝-&amp;ndash;昏君，快快找我!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2018.1 暖暖日记 （八岁二个月）</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 2018.1 暖暖日记 （八岁二个月）" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;131-18&#34;&gt;1.31. 18
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天我想不出什么好玩的，所以我打算要写无聊的事。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;比方今天我一到学校，首先有了AYMA的欢迎大邀请，然后我们一起下去上体育课。同学们都在玩篮球，可是我非常怕那个球，那么大个球，我怎么能不怕呢，我只能躲在角落里，等休息时间。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;中午，我陪AYMA采了一点很奇怪的东西，绿色的，上面毛绒绒的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;放学回家后， 我花了两个小时把两本书看了两遍，还完成了这两本书的考试，考了两个十分高的分数，都是八十六分。妈妈考试之前给我了一个帮助方法就是，碰到实在不会选的答案让屁股帮我选，拍拍屁股然后问它答案是A还是B。妈妈说屁股有时候可能会比脑袋聪明。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;别问我为什么没考100分，Reading Town 5C的书对我这个三年级的小宝宝来说应该是非常非常难的，5C的意思是五年级的C，是五年级的最高的LEVEL。Reading Town的书都是NEWSBERRY得奖的书，我不太喜欢，得奖的书都很无聊。今天这两本书其实就非常的无聊。一本是讲一个男孩不停的在给他最喜欢的AUTHOR写信，另外一本书是讲一个小孩用枪救他的妈妈。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈看到分数，眯眯笑，笑眯眯地夸我：“这么短时间就看完了两本书还考好了？! 太棒啦！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我开心地说：“我就是这么棒棒的！我的脑袋不用屁股来帮忙，她已经够聪明啦！！！！！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;148&#34;
	height=&#34;111&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_10782_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_0_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_10782_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;12718&#34;&gt;1.27.18
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;大病毒的最后一天也就是大病毒第⑥天，就是暖暖的平安之日。 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_1.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;86&#34;
	height=&#34;55&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_1_hu7f78d15674bee79cc2bb54271fb78212_2394_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_1_hu7f78d15674bee79cc2bb54271fb78212_2394_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;156&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;375px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;大病毒永远的走了+暖暖的退烧＝暖暖的开心&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这次生病我又喝了很多小柴胡，小柴胡是一种药。妈妈为什么这么喜欢小柴胡？每次我看见杯子里有小柴胡，我都看见她和她的亲爱的老公姜汤在一起。她们两个最喜欢在一起的。你知道姜汤和小柴胡生的孩子是谁吗？她们的孩子是世界出名的珍珠奶茶。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其实什么是真的快速的退烧方法呢？答案是就是不停的玩，玩是最最有效的治疗方式。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;12618-image_2jpg&#34;&gt;1.26.18 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_2.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;303&#34;
	height=&#34;134&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_2_hucae3011b61e8a7b99e6d9d33652909f1_18463_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_2_hucae3011b61e8a7b99e6d9d33652909f1_18463_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;226&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;542px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我已经是大病毒五天了，今天说说喝果汁的恐惧。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;果汁是一个非常难吃的东西，只是名字叫的好听一点，因为如果汁不叫的好听一点的话，任何人都会一下子疯掉的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈的大道理为什么暖暖不能不吃果汁：平时完全不吃蔬菜，也很少吃水果，如果再不吃果汁会变小臭臭的&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;但是吃果汁是天下所有的宝宝们的最最可怕的恶梦，她们都非常害怕有人每天会喂一大碗果汁 。 所以宝宝们天天都在练习被喂果汁时的鬼脸和反抗，还有大哭。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你可千万不要嘲笑她们，因为我喝的果汁是蔬菜汁！包括芹菜，西兰花，西红柿，胡萝卜，茄子。。。。。。这样听上去也很难吃吧！！你吓的得恐惧病了吗？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;12518&#34;&gt;1.25.18
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我已经是大病毒四天了，怎么把咳嗽治的完美&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;一想到治病肯定一定马上想到是西医的方法吗？不是！是中医的方法吗？也不是！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;放弃了吗？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;告诉你吧，是宝宝们的方法！因为很多宝宝都不知道咳嗽的时候还要喝难喝的药。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你现在知道了吧，这是打给宝宝们看到！所以如果你不是个宝宝的话，请马上退出！！!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;退出了吗？没退出的话我等你们。。。。。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;宝宝们，我现在告诉你们，把咳嗽治的完美方法就是喝珍珠奶茶！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;听完后如果你吃惊的话，说明你是个家长，请快快退！如果你是个的宝宝的话，你应该现在在很开心的鼓掌，回家告诉你妈妈别让你喝小青龙了吧！！！！！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S只有妈妈不算一个大人，姐姐和爸爸都不允许看&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;12418-image_3jpg&#34;&gt;1.24.18 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_3.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;67&#34;
	height=&#34;67&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_3_hubcb769753319a932cb3f8d3b9be0edef_2425_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_3_hubcb769753319a932cb3f8d3b9be0edef_2425_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我已经是大病毒三天了，你是不是觉得我因为发烧就没力气去欺负别人了？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果你是这样认为的话就完全错了，如果我是个大病毒的话我能把姐姐和爸爸都变成大大 病毒。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在我生病躺在床上的时候，妈妈经常开窗，说是让风把病毒带走，我很疑惑大大病毒会是想要自由还是想要在我身边&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我可不想要大大病毒老陪着我，这样我烧就永远也不会好了，如果大大病毒们不陪我玩的话，我可能会好。姐姐和爸爸总是要到我这个大大病毒房间凑热闹，不停的抱我，还就不走了，他们是想也变成大大病毒的滋味吗？尽管来！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS：妈妈今天又把我所有的课都取消了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;12318&#34;&gt;1.23.18
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;发烧VS饿&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这次我发烧的经验就是：如果发烧你就完全不可能觉得饿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果你发烧了，即使对面有你最最喜欢的吃的东西，也只有胃口吃一点点。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这样非常难受。因为想吃的东西，但是没胃口吃。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天妈妈给我喝了好几碗药，我觉得是药在这个世界上喝的最饱的东西了，我感受到小肚子要爆炸了！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1222018&#34;&gt;1.22.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我今天一早上起发现发高烧了，莫名其妙的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我最关心的还是发高烧怎么退烧？？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;首先看书是没用的，躺着也没用的，吃面也一样没用，在沙发底下看I PAD上次是有用的，吃烤串上次也是有用的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;那怎么办？我今天试验下来跑步有一点点用处，我最喜欢的方法还是在妈妈的怀里赖着。早上妈妈陪着我学了四首唐诗，两首是讲花花的，还有两首是讲秋天的，我喜欢花花的，最喜欢那句“可爱深红爱浅红”，美美的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_4.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;89&#34;
	height=&#34;67&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_4_hu2d97d93c34c584d1634b8152ae515fee_3356_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_4_hu2d97d93c34c584d1634b8152ae515fee_3356_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;132&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;318px&#34;
	
&gt; 发烧时，我会非常非常懒，头很不舒服，吃很多药药，撑得肚子很满，非常不舒服！我听到妈妈在和医生微信说：暖暖不喜欢喝中药，就跟妈妈更正，“不是不喜欢，是讨厌，不是喝了难受，是肚子非常不舒服，不要以为我还小，不懂，我学过语法了，在这里需要用程度最重的词。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说“你平时就需要对肚子好点，不要着凉，这样就不会生病了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看着现在鼓鼓的肚子让我突然明白了为什么我刚学的唐诗“镜天无一毫”里的天可以那么漂亮，没有云朵了，因为小云朵都跑到我肚子里来调皮了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我发高烧了，妈妈已经把我的所有的课都取消了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1212018&#34;&gt;1.21.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_5.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;57&#34;
	height=&#34;57&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_5_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_1242_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_5_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_1242_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;小土豆和冰淇淋 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_14.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;34&#34;
	height=&#34;66&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_14_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_1226_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_14_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_1226_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;51&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;123px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天去SPEECH最后一趟课，是个登台表演。出门的时候，看到妈妈，爸爸，姐姐都在换衣服，第一个反应就是“千万不要都是去看我的表演!!!!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈很可爱的傻傻的说“我们都要去当你的小土豆和冰淇淋！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我歪歪头问“听不懂，难道是吃的那种么??”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说“只要把台下的人都当成小土豆和冰淇淋，你在台上就不会害怕了，我们就是去当你的小土豆和冰淇淋！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我很调皮的问“那我表演完了可以冲下来，然后把你们这些小土豆和冰淇淋都吃的么？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说“可以啊，当你的表演完成的奖励”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“好呀，那我们走吧！”我们一家四口开开心心地出发了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P．S: 猜猜我有没有在台上害怕？有没有真的冲下台去吃小土豆和冰淇淋？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1202018image_6jpg&#34;&gt;1.20.2018&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_6.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;69&#34;
	height=&#34;71&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_6_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_4567_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_6_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_4567_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;97&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;233px&#34;
	
&gt;
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天我的日记写的是：怎么让你的宝宝，开心，快速，舒服的退烧。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;很多妈妈就不停给她们的生病发烧的宝宝喝药吃药，如果你是个小孩碰到这个问题，你是不是觉得你的妈妈老半天的让你喝几次药很烦呀？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;很多宝宝都说是的，所以这只是妈妈们喜欢的方法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;那妈妈们，你喜欢你的宝宝感到很烦么？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;也不喜欢吧。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天我就有一点点发烧了，我们本来今天要去烤串的，因为是一点点发烧，妈妈就很犹豫的带我去了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;到了那里我吃了一碗羊肉汤面和2个烤面包片和2个烤冰淇淋。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;吃完大餐以后，我烧就退了！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你是不是不信我烧就这么简单地退了呀，不信问我妈妈去。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;所以世界上的最好的退烧方法就是去吃烤串，妈妈喝酒，宝宝吃冰淇淋。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S:希望这篇日记对你会有用&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1192018&#34;&gt;1.19.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;在看这篇日记之前首先检查一下你是中国人吗？你是在中国学校吗？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果你两个都是，这个对你太简单了，不需要试了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;猜猜是什么？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;猜不到吧，。。。。。。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;就是考试考零分!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我一年级和两年级都试过想要考试考零分的，这个试验对我很interesting, 我想成为班里唯一一个考零分的小孩子，但都没成功。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你现在是不是很为我的屁股担心？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;谢谢！不用担心的，我屁股没有变成猴子屁股，因为我什么都没写也没得到我想要的零分。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;为什么我没有成功？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我琢磨了很久，想不明白，姐姐说 ，“ 大概是因为你还是有写你的名字，老师觉得你可怜，所以最后还是给了一分。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我打算在3年级再试一次，必须考零分！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_7.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;57&#34;
	height=&#34;65&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_7_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_2021_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_7_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_2021_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;87&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;210px&#34;
	
&gt;P.S :  我妈妈现在开始关心我的成绩单，她以前总说安全和健康是最重要的，可自从姐姐开始考大学，她慢慢改口变成成绩也是学生在学校里第一重要的，所以我三年级这个考零分的计划可能要泡汤了，对不起！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PPS:姐姐看了我的日记，叹口气说：“其实我好象也没得到过零分。 真的很伤心！” &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_8.gif&#34;
	width=&#34;22&#34;
	height=&#34;22&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_8_huac6bec2cd1d6f184a76a8761d79c6f74_1589_480x0_resize_box_1.gif 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_8_huac6bec2cd1d6f184a76a8761d79c6f74_1589_1024x0_resize_box_1.gif 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1172018&#34;&gt;1.17.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我今天在学校差点去学校的校长室，学校的规矩实在太多了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;你知道我犯了什么错误吗？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我什么错误也没犯，我只是用了学校的洗手间的水去做了一个小墙然后喂了一下树。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;小墙是用土，水和沙做的一个有点SOLID的东西。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;小树难道不值得得到一点干净水的吗？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果你觉得小树不值得得到一点干净的水，我送你我最最好的建议就是到神经病医院去检查一下有没有神经病。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;那个叫MONICA 的SRPERVISION就有非常严重的神经病，她都不让我用我自己的水壶做我自己想做的事情。这太没道理了！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;当MONICA说BLABLA。。。。。。一大堆话，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AYMA回说：“我能不能让校长打我一下”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MONICA很快就看穿了AYMA想快点结束的小心思，说：“我们学校不是这样的，打你一下，然后再见”最后MONICA说，“你们下次再这样，就真的要去校长室了”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_9.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;200&#34;
	height=&#34;131&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_9_hufa13ff3dead54770ca0987cbda79b9f0_6718_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_9_hufa13ff3dead54770ca0987cbda79b9f0_6718_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;152&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;366px&#34;
	
&gt;学校的规矩太多了，再说她们和他们也没有事先写一个单子，然后就跟你说，你不能做这个，和这个，和这个，。。。。。。BLABLA。。。。。。。。。。我想让妈妈打电话给校长，反映一下这个情况，我倒是也想和校长讨论一下这个问题！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1162018&#34;&gt;1.16.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_10.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;55&#34;
	height=&#34;55&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_10_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_1964_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_10_hu5296ab19d474c4695d8e0cdff58566e8_1964_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;如果你觉得世界上的所有的宝宝都是从妈妈肚子里开出来的，先告诉你一下，已经错了！书上说只有非常少数宝宝从妈妈肚子里开出来的，大部分都是从妈妈的屁股里出来的，或者是从我写的这些地方出来的：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1，有些宝宝是从蔬菜里长出来的，大部分这种宝宝长大后非常不喜欢吃蔬菜，因为她们生出来的时候没有妈妈的奶，只能吃很多很多的蔬菜，吃腻了。所以如果你的宝宝不喜欢吃蔬菜的话，她或者他可能是个蔬菜宝宝。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2，你还有可能生了一个云朵宝宝，云朵宝宝很软。如果你认识一个人叫云云或者这种名字的话，她或者他可能是个云朵宝宝。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3，还有可能你生了一个仙女宝宝，那种宝宝有一对透明的翅膀，如果你仔细的看她们的话，可能会看见她们身体旁边还有一点点图案，如果下面有一朵小云朵在吐舌头的话，能说明今天你会很开心。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4，如果你生的是一个臭臭或者一个傻傻宝宝，这种宝宝是非常容易发现，她们非常讨厌听“我是小臭臭”这样的歌。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5，超市宝宝就是一种很调皮的宝宝，她们很喜欢吃。她们非常讨厌超市。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6，最后一个，也是最多可能性的是垃圾筒宝宝，大多数妈妈都跟自己的宝宝说过，“你是垃圾筒里捡来的”，我还曾经建议过二年级的老师把她的宝宝也象我的妈妈一样把孩子放在垃圾筒里拍张照，她很认真地想了想，说：“我会考虑的”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果你生了一个宝宝，请告诉我你生的是哪种。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S:我爸爸可能就是一个云朵宝宝，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;而我的姐姐极有可能是第四种和第五种的混和宝宝&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;至于我呢，要去问我的妈妈，“我是什么宝宝？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说，“我这么看下来，只知道了我大概是仙女宝宝，你呢，可能是。。。。。。。？？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1152018&#34;&gt;1.15.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;日记VS作业&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_11.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;86&#34;
	height=&#34;71&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_11_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_6211_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_11_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_6211_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;121&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;290px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我一直以为我现在写的是日记，因为主题是暖暖日记。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;既然是日记，我就可以决定今天是写还是不写。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;可是妈妈很确定的说“不是，不是，你现在写的是一个规定的作业”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我提问道，“既然这是作业，那为什么主题是暖暖日记？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈很兴奋的回答说“这个问题问的非常好，因为日记就是一个每日都要做的记录，每日是每天，记是记录，所以每天需要做的记录，就是作业的意思”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我听了觉得很无聊，只能说“你不能说的更有道理一点的吗？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈把眼睛睁得大大的，“你不觉得这听上去已经是最有道理，最正确的吗”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;爸爸在旁边听后凑热闹，“每件事情都是人生的作业” 【你是不是觉得爸爸的话听上去很象唐孙】&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS：我爸爸就是唐孙，唐孙就是一半唐僧一半孙悟空，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;一边念着阿弥陀佛，一边教你怎么打妖精。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2018113&#34;&gt;2018.1.13
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天一个可恶的人把我的妈妈冻死了，更可恶的是他把妈妈饿死了，你肯定想那个人是谁呢？你就猜猜看吧。我妈妈早饭都没吃就去姐姐的同学家长聚会，会上妈妈只吃了一小块面包，然后到下午一点才散会，妈妈刚刚走到街上一个人就拉住她然后跟她BLABLA。。。。。。。。。讲家长会喜欢听的东西，为了姐姐考大学有更多的学校消息，妈妈只好在街上站着和她聊了一个多小时。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;回家来妈妈第1件事就是开壁炉，第2，拿暖宝宝和热水袋，第3喝热水，第4，一直说冷死了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;现在猜猜看那个可恶的人是谁，你想知道吗？是姐姐！因为那个把妈妈拉住的人是一直在讲姐姐的事。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS：我和爸爸妈妈吃晚饭的饭店旁边有CHATTIME，爸爸妈妈不让我去，我不开心。可是，妈妈说明天可以带我去任何我想要的蛋糕店。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2018112&#34;&gt;2018.1.12
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天在学校，我和ELLA去LOST AND FOUND整理东西。我拿方块的纸做了一个FORTUNE TELLER，可以告诉你的FORTUNE，我做好给ELLA玩,她翻到了”她爱的一个人”，她告诉我她爱一个男孩宝宝，是个婴儿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她问我有没有爱的男孩子，我告诉她“我没有”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说“你只是不承认”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我说“我真的没有”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说“你有的。“&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我看她这么坚持，于是我放弃了，说，“那你说说看”，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说我爱ANDREW，我说“没有，他是我的敌人。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后她说我爱JAMES，我一边叫一边喊“不可能，没有！他是我教室里的第一敌人”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后我说‘PROVE IT”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;她说“我来的那天，你的眼睛不停的往他们俩看。”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;五分钟整理时间到了，我们要回到班上去。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;一路上我还在想我是怎么爱上两个我的敌人了呢？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS：今天是我最LUCKY的DAY, 我现在在吃哈跟达斯雪糕。我已经一年半没吃雪糕，雪糕说它很想我，很想我吃  它。我想我最爱的应该是哈跟达斯雪糕，而不是男孩子。&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_12.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;82&#34;
	height=&#34;86&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_12_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_5454_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_12_hu813f91f2032290c9b9964618a3664e29_5454_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;95&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;228px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1112018&#34;&gt;1.11.2018
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天妈妈买了两杯bubble tea，现在家里有两杯bubble tea和一碗鸡汤。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我现在要开始面对的问题就是bubble tea VS鸡汤，小孩子和大人喜欢哪样？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;因为所有的小孩子在我们班都喜欢bubble tea超过鸡汤，所以小孩子是100 PERCENT喜欢bubble tea。关于小孩子是不是所有的小孩子都喜欢bubble tea这个问题，妈妈提出来了。她问“外国孩子也喜欢吗”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“当然”我说“AYMA就很喜欢，不过她是一半的外国人”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“纯的外国人呢”妈妈继续问&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“也一样的”爸爸说，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“真的吗？”妈妈显得很吃惊&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“是的，美国很好的大学旁边如果有bubble tea店，一样很受欢迎。”爸爸说&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我以后一定要去一个有bubble tea店的大学！！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;然后现在再来说说bubble tea VS鸡汤，家长喜欢哪个？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;大部分的家长都喜欢鸡汤，因为：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第1鸡汤很健康&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第2 bubble tea 对家长来说是垃圾食品。因为她们（妈妈们）和他们（爸爸们）都觉得bubble tea里面的bubble是塑料做的（事实上是用面 粉做的）。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;所以大概也是100 PERCENT。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;既然都是100 PERCENT，bubble tea VS鸡汤，怎么判断哪个赢呢。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;既然都是100 PERCENT，bubble tea VS鸡汤，只能两个都赢呗 。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;其实我想要bubble tea 赢的 &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_13.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;94&#34;
	height=&#34;94&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_13_hu39893eb2fa3b39704164f2eaacef99e3_2823_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018.1-%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0-%E5%85%AB%E5%B2%81%E4%BA%8C%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88/image_13_hu39893eb2fa3b39704164f2eaacef99e3_2823_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;100&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;240px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2018110&#34;&gt;2018.1.10
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我今天在和AYMA看一本书叫I am Pusheen the cat . Pusheen的妹妹是STORMY。看到书里有一页说她们都有魔棒，我和AYMA很羡慕。所以我们RECESS的时候拿了一根木头然后没完没了的磨。我觉得这样不会成功的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;后来我们上课时能有IPAD, 我们就偷偷的查怎么做哈里波特的魔棒，我想做特别的可爱的。你知道CINNAMOROLL的咖啡店里的玫瑰茶是怎么样的吗？玫瑰茶上有一朵云，我想要在魔棒上放差不多的东西。因为我最近我迷上了小白，所以好像有点偷了她的想法。其实就是把一个筷子打扮的漂亮一点，做成我们自己想要的样子的磨棒。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果成功的话我会告诉你的，明天见，日记。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2018，暖暖的中文日记起步了</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 01:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 2018，暖暖的中文日记起步了" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;201819&#34;&gt;2018.1.9
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我有一个玩具叫CINNAMOROLL，我要讲讲她的来历；有一个小女孩在一家咖啡馆工作，有一天那个小女孩看见CINNAMOROLL上有一只小兔子。她想，这只小兔肯定是被我的CINNAMOROLL蛋糕 吸引过来的。果然，那个小兔子飞过来了，仔细一看，好巧！那个小兔子的尾巴也是CINNAMROLL蛋糕的形状的！所以现在这个小兔子也叫CINNAMOROLL这个名字。她的中文名字叫小白。她还开了一家咖啡馆呢。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这是她的咖啡馆的照片&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;374&#34;
	height=&#34;264&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_0_hu2261447e1d2350d3ba7d2e0c6725359a_105414_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_0_hu2261447e1d2350d3ba7d2e0c6725359a_105414_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;141&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;340px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS: 我现在知道我为什么这么喜欢CINNAMOROLL了吗？第一，是我的朋友给我的，第二，我妈妈最喜欢的就是小白，第三，跟我爸爸的名字有缘份，这是怎么回事？不告诉你。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201818&#34;&gt;2018.1.8
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天是开学第一天，没有好事情，但是有坏事情发生。总共有2件坏事情，我本来不想说，可是妈妈说今天的日记就写写发生什么坏事情，也是蛮好的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;所以我来讲讲这2件坏事情&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.  我在RECESS的时候发现我口袋有60块钱的学费。我和AYMA在HIDEOUT做了一点淡妆，所以我想去洗手间去检查一下我的妆。我看见校长来了，我大声的叫了一声“我去洗手间！”校长没听见。然后我回我的班去了。校长也跟来了，他觉得我在逃跑，他还告诉我，在我跑到洗手间的路上把 60块钱掉了，然后我把钱拿回来了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.下午的时候，AYMA想做TREEHOUSE, 我和GRACE想守学校的规矩，不想再伤害树了，因为我们已经和AYMA已经犯了学校很多规矩。AYMA还是个很坚持的孩子，哪怕刚从校长室回来，她想好的事情从来不会放弃。当我们很真实地告诉AYMA我们的想法的时候，AYMA就很生气，说，“做你们想做的事去吧”，然后就跑走了。她生气的时候还是蛮可爱的，脸会喷红喷红的。我希望明天和AYMA和好。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201817&#34;&gt;2018.1.7
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天妈妈在跟我聊《爱花的牛》的Core Values&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我突然说:“我也有Core Values”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说“说说看？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“有用VS没用”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;妈妈说，“很有意思，STOP，不在这里说了，今天当日记写”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;所以今天我打算写我自己的Core Values：有用VS没用&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;列5个有用的例子和5个没有的例子来说明：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;现在我开始打“有用”的：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1．我勤劳的时候会帮妈妈拿手机，手机充电，和各种她不愿意起身去拿的东西。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2．我会抱CINNAMIROLL，这是我的新玩具&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3．我会烦姐姐，这很有用的，因为姐姐生气的时候很可爱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4．我能帮家里人吃掉他们都不爱的垃圾食品呢&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5．我会咬人，主要是姐姐，肚子饿的时候咬一口是很有用的&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;接着轮到写没用：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1．我懒的时候不会妈妈的手机充电，她只能让姐姐去帮她。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2．我有时候只管吃和睡不管妈妈了，好吧，我还是会抱抱妈妈的&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3．我喝BUBBLE TEA的时候我会象爱花的牛一样不管妈妈了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4．有时候我非常懒，喜欢就躺在那里不动&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5．有时候我会抱妈妈不动就躺在哪儿&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我在学“爷爷一定用办法”的Core Values的时候学过“没用VS有用”不是个相反的关系，而是个CYCLE的关系，天下万物生于有，有生于无。这又回到了我上面的谈论，勤劳的时候我能感觉自己是有用的，懒的时候我觉得是舒服的，这种舒服的感受也是有用的，也满好玩的。我觉得今天就打到这里就好了，明天见&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201816&#34;&gt;2018.1.6
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;昨天CYNTHIA来我们家SLEEPOVER，是一点开始的在画画班画了小鸟，然后我们回家，吃了甜品，玩了购物，还玩了化妆。。。。。一直到早上2点还在聊天。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天早上九点家长们还没起来我们就起来了，玩了购物：我买了有个玩具，名字忘记了。然后一点又去了的画画课，我们做了一个天使帽和小屋子。CYNTHIA和我想今天继续SLEEPOVER，可是她爸爸要回中国差不多一个月，她的妈妈想要她今天晚上陪陪她爸爸，所以我们不能继续SLEEPOVER。再说今天晚上我要和我的UNCLE PETER吃饭。我希望能有2天的SLEEPOVER&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201814&#34;&gt;2018.1.4
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天我画了一个很可爱的兔子，如果以后这只小兔子会很严肃的看电脑怎么办？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_1.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;1175&#34;
	height=&#34;1345&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_1_huca01535f756546844ca90a32cf012aee_343735_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2018%E6%9A%96%E6%9A%96%E7%9A%84%E4%B8%AD%E6%96%87%E6%97%A5%E8%AE%B0%E8%B5%B7%E6%AD%A5%E4%BA%86/image_1_huca01535f756546844ca90a32cf012aee_343735_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;87&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;209px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1， 把他们的电脑没收，如果她们还严肃就PLAN2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2， 给她们一个胡萝卜&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3， 让她看一个其他兔子睡觉的照片&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4， 叫她的妈妈抱抱她&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS：那些兔子其实是一个大人的例子，我要回去继续画画了，BYEBYE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201813&#34;&gt;2018.1.3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;我三九天爸爸带我在COSCO买了哈跟达斯雪糕,买了一盒，可是妈妈说三九天不能吃哈跟达斯雪糕 , 理由是：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1，哈跟达斯雪糕是冰的，所以是寒冷的，我觉得没道理：因为妈妈在昨年的昨年的冬天买过一模一样的哈跟达斯雪糕回来给我和姐姐吃。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2，会着凉的，这点还是没道理：昨年的昨年我就没着凉。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;现在我再来讲讲我可以吃哈跟达斯雪糕的理由：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1, 今天还是新年，新年应该开开心心的吃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2, 我吃不下的LEFTOVERS姐姐能吃, 因为她肚子更大。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;让我总结一下：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1妈妈没道理&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2妈妈还是没道理&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;所以我能吃哈跟达斯雪糕了YAY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201812&#34;&gt;2018.1.2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天我一直在做作业，为什么大人可以每天一直在看电脑呢？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;让我纠结一下为什么这样不公平。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;小孩做作业时大人在看电脑&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;大人在看电脑文章时不抱宝宝了&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;大人看电脑时候很严肃的时候很可怕&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;还有好多好多理由我也懒得再说 . 所以我现在回去看书了 BYEBYE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;201811&#34;&gt;2018．1.1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天我和Cynthia又有了一个Play date。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我去她家时是中午12：00，一直玩到晚上8：00，回家时天已经很黑了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我们先看了一个电影，看到要杀一只牛的时候我觉得有一点可怕。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看完电影后我们SHOPPING了,买了小孩子的化妆品。在Cynthia家一边化妆一边吃PIZZA。那里最好玩的，可是很可惜只有1个半小时，因为我们又要去吃饭了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在饭店吃龙虾和烤鸭的时候我和Cynthia和 Jason  , Jason 是个男孩, 玩了一点小游戏，我很开心。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天玩得好开心！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我希望妈妈会让我和CYNTHIA再有一个SLEEPOVER.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2017-1231&#34;&gt;2017. 12.31
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;今天是我和Cynthia的play date ，她12：45分来我家的，我画了小兔子, Cynthia画了杯珍珠奶茶，我们还玩了TUNNELTOWN，4:45分的时候我们都无聊了。在我们玩Monopoly 的时候她的妈妈来接她了。我不想她，因为我明天要和她再有一个play date。我会prepare好，这样我们能吃chocolate。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/image_2.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/image_3.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Inanimate Alice</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 13:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_1.png" alt="Featured image of post Inanimate Alice" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1106&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_1_hucac11b2b0ec21f0823f85cd29b5ae6a0_1113784_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_1_hucac11b2b0ec21f0823f85cd29b5ae6a0_1113784_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;80&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;192px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1062&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_2_huc7d68a5cae6cee7c0c6db62731bd2971_793016_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/inanimate-alice/image_2_huc7d68a5cae6cee7c0c6db62731bd2971_793016_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;76&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;184px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>RP: When Hilter Stole Pink Rabit</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post RP: When Hilter Stole Pink Rabit" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;940&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_0_hu2d20c6c5574dffd1e2f276eff43112e0_1362431_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_0_hu2d20c6c5574dffd1e2f276eff43112e0_1362431_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;68&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;163px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1308&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_1_huaf1bb8ba7d72483929fe07e647e8c889_1573328_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/rp-when-hilter-stole-pink-rabit/image_1_huaf1bb8ba7d72483929fe07e647e8c889_1573328_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;94&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;227px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>RP:Number The Stars</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 01:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post RP:Number The Stars" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;第一次写读书笔记&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1028&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_0_hu15faacf98e63ae6d2a91e0bb56a02935_1757468_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_0_hu15faacf98e63ae6d2a91e0bb56a02935_1757468_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;178px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1038&#34;
	height=&#34;1380&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_1_hu13503fe6ad21a8a86b3adf42f1aee00b_1343361_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/rpnumber-the-stars/image_1_hu13503fe6ad21a8a86b3adf42f1aee00b_1343361_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;75&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;180px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Fairy Adventure</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/fairy-adventure/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/fairy-adventure/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/fairy-adventure/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post Fairy Adventure" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fairy Adventure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Freya 2017.9.23&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/fairy-adventure/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1610&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/fairy-adventure/image_0_hue901bad80b28727c1eafba24bc4ab870_1456783_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/fairy-adventure/image_0_hue901bad80b28727c1eafba24bc4ab870_1456783_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;85&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;205px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello, My name is Rose. I want be a flower fairy one day when I wake up. I wanted to go and pick flower. So I ate my breakfast fast and went to pick flower. When I picked flower I saw a flower that was lighting up. I picked it and suddenly I was in a magical garden. I first peeled a little bit of flower and I heard a ticking voice. That said “why are you peel me” and a fairy flow out and the fairy called Merry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Merry wisper to Winter, another fairy who is Merry’s sister “Rose is a people,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Well,” Winter said with a wave of her wands ”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then Rose turn into a fairy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Yeah! Now I am a fairy, I’m so happy,” says Rose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you want to go to Noth Pole?” Winter asked,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Of course I want”, Rose said ,”I never been to Noth Pole .”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then in a blink of an eye,they are in Noth Pole .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ so cold,” said Rose,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No worry,” Winter said, “I didn’t forget about jacket.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They start walking. Suddely they saw Santa Clause. They made snow angel, snowman, and snow ball fight together and they have a lot of fun!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Ｉneed to go back home.” Rose said when they are tired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Do you need a lift back home?” Santa Clause asked&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“yes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then in a blink of eye, Rose ,Winter and Santa Clause drank hot chocolate back at Rose’s home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a brillian day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Sorciere</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/sorciere/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 04:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/sorciere/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/sorciere/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post Sorciere" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/sorciere/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;880&#34;
	height=&#34;1262&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/sorciere/image_0_hu76b8ef1075ff345d90e77d5d62ccdd64_974361_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/sorciere/image_0_hu76b8ef1075ff345d90e77d5d62ccdd64_974361_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;69&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;167px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>TO MOMMY</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/to-mommy/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 16:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/to-mommy/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/to-mommy/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post TO MOMMY" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2017.2.23&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/to-mommy/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;802&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/to-mommy/image_0_hu4bc6a01b37663711b981ab9853c27d49_1418070_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/to-mommy/image_0_hu4bc6a01b37663711b981ab9853c27d49_1418070_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;172&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;412px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Carotte</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/carotte/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 08:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/carotte/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/carotte/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post Carotte" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2017.2.12&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;是读两本小书还是写一篇小文？今天就写个故事吧&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/carotte/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1298&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/carotte/image_0_hu2ea41dfc4163bd8cc5ac4af0acfb88cb_1518529_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/carotte/image_0_hu2ea41dfc4163bd8cc5ac4af0acfb88cb_1518529_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;77&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;186px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>法文WRITING也走出了第一步！</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 06:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 法文WRITING也走出了第一步！" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;2016年10月，小暖迈出了法文WRITING的第一步！记录一笔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;自创的小故事和学校READING里挑两本书写的读书笔记&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1046&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_0_huf624e9c21a7a8b6d80b3495fca340f7c_1251955_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_0_huf624e9c21a7a8b6d80b3495fca340f7c_1251955_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;131&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;316px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1018&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_1_hu6ee5fea7b04ce949400cc5f3768f2b29_908885_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_1_hu6ee5fea7b04ce949400cc5f3768f2b29_908885_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;135&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;325px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1250&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_2_hub119fd625100b4a18a50d8d1810a1adc_2292445_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_2_hub119fd625100b4a18a50d8d1810a1adc_2292445_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1344&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_3_huc94fc925a4899ceeb1d326f9093fda00_1159081_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_3_huc94fc925a4899ceeb1d326f9093fda00_1159081_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;80&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;193px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_4.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1250&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_4_hu9a460c004e15164c11d89e12a78f0b29_2385457_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%B3%95%E6%96%87writing%E4%B9%9F%E8%B5%B0%E5%87%BA%E4%BA%86%E7%AC%AC%E4%B8%80%E6%AD%A5/image_4_hu9a460c004e15164c11d89e12a78f0b29_2385457_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>自制的小画书：Decorate My Home</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 00:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 自制的小画书：Decorate My Home" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;880&#34;
	height=&#34;854&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_0_hu8544694e44a15507ce6946a120d4d8d9_721419_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_0_hu8544694e44a15507ce6946a120d4d8d9_721419_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;103&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;247px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;880&#34;
	height=&#34;516&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_1_hu7cb229b4bc7ea817ca29f0c0644ff744_487244_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_1_hu7cb229b4bc7ea817ca29f0c0644ff744_487244_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;170&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;409px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;880&#34;
	height=&#34;534&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_2_hu410a22c7e699cb2c94629d114be51814_444970_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_2_hu410a22c7e699cb2c94629d114be51814_444970_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;164&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;395px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_3.png&#34;
	width=&#34;880&#34;
	height=&#34;532&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_3_hub9ca8a16eeb82369d7df1cc71e0bbab3_455303_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E8%87%AA%E5%88%B6%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E7%94%BB%E4%B9%A6decorate-my-home/image_3_hub9ca8a16eeb82369d7df1cc71e0bbab3_455303_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;165&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;396px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Bluey</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 02:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post Bluey" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1036&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_0_hue68b5714a36487451f3f4b5c899adbd0_1207424_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_0_hue68b5714a36487451f3f4b5c899adbd0_1207424_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1036&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_1_huf8e5853052fc48d05d7d97bbb7df7f8a_1081042_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/bluey/image_1_huf8e5853052fc48d05d7d97bbb7df7f8a_1081042_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>76@365 Casey</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 01:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 76@365 Casey" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1250&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_0_huae3f4be07b4d15bdf15745e022ef2ce7_1983231_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_0_huae3f4be07b4d15bdf15745e022ef2ce7_1983231_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1036&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_1_hu8702c0f31b8f0de211588a3c945364e8_1102792_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-casey/image_1_hu8702c0f31b8f0de211588a3c945364e8_1102792_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>76@365 2016.3.15故事画：花丛里的小天使</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-2016.3.15%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB%E8%8A%B1%E4%B8%9B%E9%87%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E5%A4%A9%E4%BD%BF/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 01:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-2016.3.15%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB%E8%8A%B1%E4%B8%9B%E9%87%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E5%A4%A9%E4%BD%BF/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-2016.3.15%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB%E8%8A%B1%E4%B8%9B%E9%87%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E5%A4%A9%E4%BD%BF/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 76@365 2016.3.15故事画：花丛里的小天使" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;小女孩子 的世界真的很美好&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-2016.3.15%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB%E8%8A%B1%E4%B8%9B%E9%87%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E5%A4%A9%E4%BD%BF/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1202&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-2016.3.15%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB%E8%8A%B1%E4%B8%9B%E9%87%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E5%A4%A9%E4%BD%BF/image_0_hu0ddfb2def656f57b6bb6c05e64a5696c_1716645_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/76@365-2016.3.15%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB%E8%8A%B1%E4%B8%9B%E9%87%8C%E7%9A%84%E5%B0%8F%E5%A4%A9%E4%BD%BF/image_0_hu0ddfb2def656f57b6bb6c05e64a5696c_1716645_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;72&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;173px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, there is a little village called Angelville.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Angelville there is nothing but a castle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In that castle there are a lot of angels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the most special thing is a flower !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few angels take care of the flower.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some feed it with pixsdust and some make the pixsdust and some live up for pixsdust and some just sleep and watch TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to know more just flip the page and look at the picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok,So 1,2,3,Done&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>故事画</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 19:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 故事画" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1034&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0_hu2e9a21ffd3dbb4b9941e4608633b39d0_1073241_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0_hu2e9a21ffd3dbb4b9941e4608633b39d0_1073241_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;320px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1250&#34;
	height=&#34;1667&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_1_hua49ad59b4aa5c5a97ed860257a69c3a8_1779963_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_1_hua49ad59b4aa5c5a97ed860257a69c3a8_1779963_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_2.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1036&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_2_hu835a32064c081406067f2545dda11e8a_1272200_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_2_hu835a32064c081406067f2545dda11e8a_1272200_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2015.12.6 故事画：I am a cute little girl</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 03:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 2015.12.6 故事画：I am a cute little girl" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_0.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;690&#34;
	height=&#34;760&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_0_hu78fcefe3cfe5d928ba73fdc1bb6b1ee7_199800_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_0_hu78fcefe3cfe5d928ba73fdc1bb6b1ee7_199800_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;90&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;217px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_1.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;690&#34;
	height=&#34;442&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_1_hu22a67ba1e450495081e26ea5935f5904_129600_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_1_hu22a67ba1e450495081e26ea5935f5904_129600_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;156&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;374px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_2.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;690&#34;
	height=&#34;518&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_2_hubecc9ef9a8dade92c4fc36ca6242e2b4_171106_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_2_hubecc9ef9a8dade92c4fc36ca6242e2b4_171106_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_3.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;690&#34;
	height=&#34;435&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_3_hu21ae599146d7cca9ef1e62669888487e_146464_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.6-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BBi-am-a-cute-little-girl/image_3_hu21ae599146d7cca9ef1e62669888487e_146464_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;158&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;380px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2015.12.3  故事画</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 02:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 2015.12.3  故事画" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1390&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0_hudb6756f6c9366a0443d6d1b232602b2f_1264809_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_0_hudb6756f6c9366a0443d6d1b232602b2f_1264809_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;99&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;238px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1366&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_1_hue75c82a707b33dfa52b87f293893996b_1100569_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.3-%E6%95%85%E4%BA%8B%E7%94%BB/image_1_hue75c82a707b33dfa52b87f293893996b_1100569_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;101&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;242px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2015.12.1  My Browine Squirrel</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2015 12:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_0.png" alt="Featured image of post 2015.12.1  My Browine Squirrel" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_0.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1036&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_0_hu074cc071925c354d7c2df05e8e526be9_1368206_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_0_hu074cc071925c354d7c2df05e8e526be9_1368206_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_1.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1380&#34;
	height=&#34;1036&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_1_hu7c7ceb8e9be73ae03c6fda05bed5331b_1194846_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015.12.1-my-browine-squirrel/image_1_hu7c7ceb8e9be73ae03c6fda05bed5331b_1194846_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;133&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;319px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>2015 口头作文四则</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/2015-%E5%8F%A3%E5%A4%B4%E4%BD%9C%E6%96%87%E5%9B%9B%E5%88%99/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/2015-%E5%8F%A3%E5%A4%B4%E4%BD%9C%E6%96%87%E5%9B%9B%E5%88%99/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/p/2015-%E5%8F%A3%E5%A4%B4%E4%BD%9C%E6%96%87%E5%9B%9B%E5%88%99/image_0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post 2015 口头作文四则" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;目录&#34;&gt;目录
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;#1%e6%88%91%e9%aa%91%e5%8d%95%e8%bd%a6&#34; &gt;1 我骑单车&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;#2-%e5%b0%8f%e7%8b%97%e5%8e%bb%e6%9a%96%e6%9a%96%e5%ae%b6&#34; &gt;2 小狗去暖暖家&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;#3%e6%9f%94%e6%9f%94&#34; &gt;3 柔柔&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;#4%e4%bb%8a%e5%a4%a9%e6%98%af%e6%83%85%e4%ba%ba%e8%8a%82&#34; &gt;4 今天是情人节&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;1我骑单车&#34;&gt;1）我骑单车
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;2015/4/13
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天我可以不用爸爸扶，不用戴护膝、护腕，只戴头盔，骑着单车，直接从山坡上冲下去，而且还是在马路中间。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;太可怕了？不怕，因为有爸爸在旁边保护呢。我一点也不怕。可是，也有过一次，我的心怦怦直跳，吓得我腿都是软的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第一次骑单车，是爸爸一直扶着我，他一点也不轻松，他说太累了，要回家了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;第二次，我一下子就学会了。我什么也不怕了，不用戴护膝、不用戴护腕，只戴头盔，一下子就从坡上冲下去了。姐姐在一旁直喊：“太可怕了，要是有汽车过来，撞上暖暖怎么办？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;因为有爸爸在一旁保护着呢，所以不用怕。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我觉得我骑车像小鸟一样，不，就是一只飞着的小鸟。因为我轻轻的一跺脚，轻松地踩轮着，而且不用费一点力气就可以上坡（爸爸在推我呢），掉头后，一下子就从山坡上冲下去了。我说我像只小鸟，可姐姐说：“你不觉得你这只小鸟还在地上吗？”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我们家只有我一个人有单车，我想可能是因为他们觉得单车太贵了，所以只有我可以骑。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;骑单车真的很快乐！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015-%E5%8F%A3%E5%A4%B4%E4%BD%9C%E6%96%87%E5%9B%9B%E5%88%99/image_0.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;440&#34;
	height=&#34;587&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/p/2015-%E5%8F%A3%E5%A4%B4%E4%BD%9C%E6%96%87%E5%9B%9B%E5%88%99/image_0_hu92a0d16792df2e0352818eefe5202ab1_126445_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/p/2015-%E5%8F%A3%E5%A4%B4%E4%BD%9C%E6%96%87%E5%9B%9B%E5%88%99/image_0_hu92a0d16792df2e0352818eefe5202ab1_126445_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;74&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;179px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;2-小狗去暖暖家&#34;&gt;2) 小狗去暖暖家
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;2015.2. 6
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;从前，有一只小狗，他要去暖暖家。他先过了一条马路，又要过一个森林。在森林里的时候，一只狗熊从草丛里跳了出来，他对小狗说，我要吃掉你。小狗说：“不行不行，因为我是狗，你是狗熊，我们都有一个狗字，所以，我们应该是好朋友。”狗熊想了想说，觉得有道理，就没有吃掉小狗。小狗继续走，走到一个房子里，房子里住着一个女巫，女巫说：“我要把你变成魔法药水。”小狗就拿来一个镜子、一个戒指，还有一个创可贴。然后，女巫在小狗后面追呀追，小狗先是丢在草地上一个镜子，因为这个镜子有魔法。女巫想了想，他继续追小狗。第二次，小狗丢了一个创可贴在草地上，女巫又想了想，他又继续追。最后，小狗丢了一个戒指到草地上，这一回， 戒指变成了一根绳子，女巫被捆了起来。小狗去了警察局，告诉警察说：“我抓了一个女巫。”警察不相信，说：“女巫？”小狗说：“是的。”警察抓住了女巫，从此，女巫就没有了。小狗继续向前走，过了马路，进了一条街，又过了一条马路，到了酒店，上了电梯，按了27楼，顺利地找到了暖暖家。进了暖暖的房间，上到了暖暖的摇篮床，大声地说：“暖暖抱！”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;3柔柔&#34;&gt;3）柔柔
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;2015.2
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我有一个小兔子，名字叫柔柔。它很软，所以叫柔柔。可是，它总想吃胡萝卜，我家没有胡萝卜呀。让它先饿着吧！现在我要去找胡萝卜了！找到了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;看，它吃得多高兴呀！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;晚上它在看星星的时候，嘴里还啃着胡萝卜呢！它睡觉都啃着呢。因为兔子最喜欢的零食就是胡萝卜了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;现在我要给小兔子出数学题了：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10+1= ？ 暖暖帮它说是 11。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;14+4=  ？ 兔子说，等于16，暖暖说应该是18。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;888888888888888，这是什么意思呢？我偷偷地告诉姐姐，是再见的意思。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;4今天是情人节&#34;&gt;4）今天是情人节
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;2015.2. 14         
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;今天是情人节，暖暖我第一次在加拿大过情人节。今天棒棒糖来到我们家了，唐老鸭也来了，小蜡笔 也来了，彩色软糖也来了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;呵呵，东西太多了。这些都是我的朋友们送给我的情人节礼物。只是，今年我没有送给他们礼物，因为我不知道。明年，我一定要给我的朋友们准备情人节礼物。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我很高兴，赶快给我的小狗狗雅飞吃块棒棒糖吧！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>六岁一个月：The Little Dog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/p/%E5%85%AD%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%80%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88the-little-dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/%E5%85%AD%E5%B2%81%E4%B8%80%E4%B8%AA%E6%9C%88the-little-dog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;2015.11.23&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-little-dog&#34;&gt;The Little Dog
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;chapter-1&#34;&gt;chapter 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One upon a time, there was a little house.In that little house lived a little dog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;chapter-2&#34;&gt;chapter 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day , the little dog went out to theforest to pick some flower to decorate his house, but suddenly a bad lion came.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He said,&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to eat you!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The little dog was not afraid because hehad a magic power!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;chapter-3&#34;&gt;chapter 3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The little dog used his magic power tofreeze the little lion and the lion didn&amp;rsquo;t know the little dog have amagic power. The little dog freezed him and at that time the little dogran away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-end&#34;&gt;THE END
&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
